<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<File xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<jobs>		
		<job>
			<JobID>114612</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time/W2 General Surgeon Needed in Southern Oregon - 114612</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Full-time/W2 General Surgeon Needed in Southern Oregon - 114612 &lt;br&gt;Pay: Competitive salary with great incentives &lt;br&gt;Extras: sign-on bonus, relocation assistance, and benefits &lt;br&gt;Location: Beautiful southern Oregon &lt;br&gt;Job Number: 114612  &lt;br&gt;#RPO</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>General Surgery</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Medford</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>112360</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time Consult Liaison Psychiatry Openings - 112360</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;Outpatient, Consult Liaison Psychiatry Positions Available. Join a passionate team of Psychiatrists who are at the frontlines of behavioral healthcare!&lt;br&gt;Position Highlights: &lt;br&gt;100% Telepsychiatry  &lt;br&gt;Hospital-Based &lt;br&gt;Consult Liaison  -  Med-Surg Floor / Emergency Room &lt;br&gt;60-min consults &amp; 30-min follow-ups  &lt;br&gt;10-hour shifts: day, night &amp; weekend options  &lt;br&gt;Flexible schedule, you pick the days of the month you want to work and can schedule 90 days out &lt;br&gt;Competitive Compensation with High Earning Potential &lt;br&gt;Fast hiring process &lt;br&gt;Will license in the states required  -  No cost for the provider with administrative support throughout the process  &lt;br&gt;All equipment provided as well as 24/7 tech support &lt;br&gt;Health, Dental, 401k, CME, PTO for W2 employee ' s +more  &lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;Completion of a 4-year ACGME Residency Program in Psychiatry &lt;br&gt;Experience in consult-liaison psychiatry &lt;br&gt;Active medical license(s) in the U.S., any State License Accepted &lt;br&gt;Will Pay for Additional Licensing  &lt;br&gt;#RPO</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Psychiatry Consult Liaison</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Austin</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>TX</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115932</JobID>
			<JobTitle>full-time psychiatrist Minnesota / Wisconsin - 115932</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Here are the details for the MN/WI full-time OP opportunity. &lt;br&gt;Setting: Out-patient  &lt;br&gt;Hours: Flexible but overall 4-5 days needed, can do Mon-Thursday 8am-5pm CST or Monday-Friday 8am-5pm CST &lt;br&gt;Patient Diagnosis:  anxiety, depression, dual diagnosis, ADHD, mood disorders, SMI  &lt;br&gt;MD must be comfortable with prescribing stimulants and other controlled substances &lt;br&gt;No on call needed after hours but will need to be available throughout shift to take refill request for patient panel or when other MDs are out &lt;br&gt;No supervision of NPs &lt;br&gt;EMR: Epic with Mychart video feature &lt;br&gt;Support and Wrap around services: Case Manager in PC offices  -  Nurse Triage Team, NP, MA &lt;br&gt;Appointment times: 60 minute initials, 30 minute follow-ups &lt;br&gt;1 hour lunch and 30 minutes of admin time each day &lt;br&gt;State Licensure needed: Wisconsin and Michigan (Iris will pay for both licensure needed, we could also go through the compact license process) &lt;br&gt;Facility Credentialing timeframe: 60-90 days  &lt;br&gt;#RPO</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Psychiatry</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Austin</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>TX</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115413</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time/Employed Position - Administrator/Director of Nursing - RN - Bronx, NY - 115413</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Full-time/Employed Position - Administrator/Director of Nursing - RN - Bronx, NY - 115413 &lt;br&gt;This position has 4 weeks PTO, benefit coverages and 401K &lt;br&gt;Title: Administrator/Director of Nursing &lt;br&gt;Schedule: Early mornings, 6: 00 AM/7: 00 AM  -  3: 00 PM/4: 00 PM, Monday  -  Friday with a Saturday every other week &lt;br&gt;Basic Details:   &lt;br&gt;Must be an active RN &lt;br&gt;Previous experience in ASC is required &lt;br&gt;GI or Endo experience is ideal &lt;br&gt;Prior leadership experience is required, a minimum of 3 years in a leadership position &lt;br&gt;Hands-on clinical role, must have experience on the floor and be comfortable working in this capacity  &lt;br&gt;Understanding of the financial aspect of reporting (i.E. Budgets, billing/revenue cycle, business needs/costs, etc.) &lt;br&gt;Strong leader who is self-sufficient and confident   &lt;br&gt;#RPO</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Nurse Practitioner</Profession>
			<Specialty>Gastroenterology</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Jamison</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>PA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115136</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time/Employed - All Ages Psychiatrist position - Oklahoma - Spanish and NP Supervision Required</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Full-time/Employed - All Ages Psychiatrist position - Oklahoma - Spanish and NP Supervision Required &lt;br&gt;Setting: Non-profit organization &lt;br&gt;License required: Oklahoma &lt;br&gt;Patient Demographics: All ages, 4 and up  -  majority child/adolescent (75%+) &lt;br&gt;This position requires someone who can provide services in Spanish and open to supervising 4 on-site NPs &lt;br&gt;State: Oklahoma &lt;br&gt;Job Number: 115136  &lt;br&gt;#RPO</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Psychiatry</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Austin</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>TX</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115135</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Fulltime/Employed - Tele MAT Psychiatrist - 115135</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Fulltime/Employed - Tele MAT Psychiatrist - 115135 &lt;br&gt;MAT position in TX &lt;br&gt;License required: Texas &lt;br&gt;Patient Demographics:  18+, with some patients receiving SUD treatment as young as 16-17 years old on rare occasion. &lt;br&gt;Patient population: A large percentage of the patients being referred for Psychiatry services will be Substance abuse (MAT) patients but will also see patients with Major Depression, Anxiety Disorder, Bipolar Disorder, Schizo disorders, and other mental health disorders. Out of the SUD &amp; MAT patient population only 30% are primarily substance use, 70% are dual diagnosis SUD.    #RPO</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Psychiatry</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Austin</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>TX</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115003</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time/Employed - Psychiatrist position - Telehealth - 115003</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Full-time/Employed - Psychiatrist position - Telehealth - 115003 &lt;br&gt;New Outpatient Opening! &lt;br&gt;IL and MO license needed (will see half of their caseload in IL and half in MO) &lt;br&gt;Ages 5-18 is ideal &lt;br&gt;Must be board certified CAD or CAD trained with Board Eligibility &lt;br&gt;Hours: 24 hours (Flexible on days of the week) If the MD needs 40 hours we are willing to flex up to Full-time &lt;br&gt;Diagnosis: anxiety, depression, ADHD, ASD &lt;br&gt;Job Number: 115003  &lt;br&gt;#RPO</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Psychiatry</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Austin</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>TX</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114886</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Fulltime Employed - Physical and Medicine Rehabilitation - PM&amp;R - Physiatrist - New Jersey</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Fulltime Employed -   Physical and Medicine Rehabilitation - PM&amp;R - Physiatrist - New Jersey &lt;br&gt;Specialty: PM&amp;R - Physiatrist&lt;br&gt;Preferred training and experience with Ultrasound guided injections, PRP, Cortisone injections   &lt;br&gt;Requirements:&lt;br&gt;Board certified or board eligible in PM&amp;R &lt;br&gt;Clear and active license in NJ or willingness to obtain NJ license (ICON can help with this)   &lt;br&gt;Incentives and Benefits Package:&lt;br&gt;Competitive base salary strong productivity bonus incentive &lt;br&gt;Full benefits including medical, dental, vision and 401k plan &lt;br&gt;Covered malpractice and CMEs   &lt;br&gt;State: New Jersey &lt;br&gt;Job number: 114886  &lt;br&gt;#RPO</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Orthopaedic Surgery</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Paramus</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>NJ</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114968</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time/ Employed - Physician Associate - PM&amp;R - Pennsylvania</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Full-time/ Employed - Physician Associate - PM&amp;R - Pennsylvania&lt;br&gt;Specialty: Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation ProviderSite: comprehensive operative and non-operative patient-centered careQualified Candidates:&lt;br&gt;Board certified or board eligible in PM&amp;R &lt;br&gt;Clear and active license in PA  or willingness to obtain PA  license  Incentives and Benefits Package:&lt;br&gt;Competitive base salary  plus strong productivity bonus incentive &lt;br&gt;Full benefits including medical, dental, vision and 401k plan &lt;br&gt;Covered malpractice and CMEs  State: PennsylvaniaJob Number: 114968 #RPO</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Orthopaedic Surgery</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Paramus</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>NJ</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114965</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time Employed - Physician Associate - PM&amp;R - New Jersey</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Full-time Employed -   Physician Associate - PM&amp;R  - New Jersey &lt;br&gt;Specialty: Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation Provider &lt;br&gt;Site: Comprehensive operative and non-operative patient-centered care  &lt;br&gt;Qualified Candidates: &lt;br&gt;Board certified or board eligible in PM&amp;R &lt;br&gt;Clear and active license in NJ or willingness to obtain NJ license &lt;br&gt;Incentives and Benefits Package: &lt;br&gt;Competitive base salary &lt;br&gt;Full benefits including medical, dental, vision and 401k plan &lt;br&gt;Covered malpractice and CMEs  &lt;br&gt;State: New Jerseyjob Number: 114965  &lt;br&gt;#RPO</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Orthopaedic Surgery</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Paramus</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>NJ</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114964</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Fulltime Employed - Physician Associate - PM&amp;R - NJ</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Fulltime Employed - Physician Associate - PM&amp;R - NJ &lt;br&gt;Qualified Candidates:&lt;br&gt;Board certified or board eligible in PM&amp;R &lt;br&gt;Clear and active license in PA or willingness to obtain PA license (ICON can help with this)   &lt;br&gt;Incentives and Benefits Package:&lt;br&gt;Competitive base salary plus strong productivity bonus incentive &lt;br&gt;Full benefits including medical, dental, vision, and 401k plan &lt;br&gt;Covered malpractice and CMEs    &lt;br&gt;#RPO</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Orthopaedic Surgery</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Paramus</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>NJ</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114416</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time Employed - Permanent Position - Long Term Care/Geriatric - MD - Frederick, MD Area</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Full-time Employed - Permanent Position - Long Term Care/Geriatric - MD - Frederick, MD Area &lt;br&gt;Specialty: IM or FAM or Primary Care - Long Term Care/Geriatric Population &lt;br&gt;Competitive pay! &lt;br&gt;State: Maryland &lt;br&gt;Job number: 114416  &lt;br&gt;#RPO</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Geriatrics</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Linthicum Heights</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>MD</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114415</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time Employed - Long Term Care/Geriatric - MD - Harford County, MD Area</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;Full-time Employed - Long Term Care/Geriatric - MD - Harford County, MD Area &lt;br&gt;Specialty: IM or FAM or Primary Care - Long-Term Care/Geriatric Population &lt;br&gt;Competitive compensation package &lt;br&gt;State: Maryland &lt;br&gt;Job Number: 114415  &lt;br&gt;#RPO</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Geriatrics</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Linthicum Heights</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>MD</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114414</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time Long Term Care/Geriatric Need in Baltimore, MD Area - 114414</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription> &lt;br&gt;Position type: IM/FAM or Primary Care Physician &lt;br&gt;Salary: Competitive &lt;br&gt;Patient type: long-term care/geriatric &lt;br&gt;Teaching is not a primary part of their role, but the competency levels of the team could vary &lt;br&gt;This opportunity offers high flexibility and increased pay &lt;br&gt;Provider will be working with clients in LTC facilities&lt;br&gt;Facility has care plan and team designed to support the overall health of the clients, many who have proven chronic illness&lt;br&gt;State: Maryland&lt;br&gt;Job Number: 114414&lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;#RPO</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Geriatrics</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Linthicum Heights</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>MD</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114223</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Psychiatry - IL/MO CAD CL Opportunity - 114223</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;Setting: ED/IP &lt;br&gt;Location: Missouri (IL is secondary license but they can start with MO) &lt;br&gt;30 Hours a week (Monday-Friday 6 hour days) flexible on hours but will need someone who can be available for morning shifts. No weekends or evenings required &lt;br&gt;Ages: 7-21 (MD will have parent contact information) &lt;br&gt;Diagnosis: SPMI, high acuity, SMI &lt;br&gt;Initial Evaluations are 60 minutes plus depending on the complexity, follow ups are 30 minutes plus  &lt;br&gt;Patient value is normally 3-5 consults per 6 hour shift, when you are not completing consults you will be working with care team members, completing admin time, and reaching out to parents &lt;br&gt;MD will collaborate with triage staff and assist with bridge care until the patient can be routed to out-patient services. There is a bit more continuum of care versus standard ED/CL model.   &lt;br&gt;EMR used is EPIC  &lt;br&gt;Job Number: 114223&lt;br&gt;#RPO</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Psychiatry</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Austin</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>TX</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114222</JobID>
			<JobTitle>PT or FT Adult Psychiatrist Needed - 114222</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;Adult Spanish-speaking demographic &lt;br&gt;Outpatient  -  IL (Multi-Sites \ Centralized scheduling)&lt;br&gt;Diagnoses:  Bipolar, mood disorders, serious mental illness interfering with everyday life, substance use,  schizophrenia, schizo-affect, psychosis. Dual Diagnosis.&lt;br&gt;Languages: English &amp; Spanish Bi-Lingual&lt;br&gt;Hours: Monday  -  Friday 8-5 CST&lt;br&gt;Appointment times: 60/30 or 60/20 Depending on the patient ' s acuity level&lt;br&gt;Patients per day: 16-18&lt;br&gt;Suboxone waiver: Required&lt;br&gt;Call: 8A  -  8A phone coverage (rotating weekend and holiday schedule)&lt;br&gt;#RPO &lt;br&gt;  </JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Psychiatry</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Austin</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>TX</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114221</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Telhealth FT Child and Adolescent Psychiatry Position - 114221</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription> &lt;br&gt;Specialty: Child/Adolescent Psychiatry - Telehealth &lt;br&gt;Salary: Competitive &lt;br&gt;Setting: Outpatient center for Child and Adolescent  &lt;br&gt;Age range: 4-21 yrs. Old &lt;br&gt;Patient population: ASD, anxiety, depression, behavioral disorders, ADHD &lt;br&gt;Appointment times: 60-minute initials, 30-minute follow-ups &lt;br&gt;EMR: EPIC &lt;br&gt;Patients are seen from their homes; this clinic has a great process in place for patients to be seen remotely and has been operating remotely since COVID &lt;br&gt;Hours per week: 24 - 40 hours (Fridays preferred) &lt;br&gt;Patient volume: 10-13 patients per day &lt;br&gt;Wrap-around services: Neurologists, psychiatrists, psychologists, nurses, speech-language pathologists, occupational therapists, family resource specialists, education coordinator, inpatient, and IOP. &lt;br&gt;No on-call, supervision, or x-waiver is required &lt;br&gt;Will license! &lt;br&gt;New Fellows are welcome to apply!   &lt;br&gt;Job Number: 114221&lt;br&gt;#RPO</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Psychiatry Child</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Austin</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>TX</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>112286</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time Adult TelePsychiatry Job | Need PA License - 112286</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription> &lt;br&gt;Start: when credentialed (approximately 90-days)&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;Schedule:  Monday- Friday (remote)&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;Full-time Adult Psychiatrist&lt;br&gt;W2 or 1099&lt;br&gt;Telepsychiatry&lt;br&gt;Diagnoses: Standard range of community diagnoses, with an expected prevalence of mood disorder, anxiety disorder and substance use disorder (SUD). Patients with acute needs will be transferred to onsite Geisinger specialists or local CSBs.&lt;br&gt;EMR: EPIC&lt;br&gt;NP Supervision&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;Requirements: &lt;br&gt;Active license in PA&lt;br&gt;BC/BE&lt;br&gt;No malpractice history&lt;br&gt;Experience with adults&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;#DH</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Psychiatry Adult</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Austin</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>TX</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>rebecca.kenney@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115650</JobID>
			<JobTitle>permanent - Regional Vice President ASC Operations - 115650</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;Type: Direct Hire &lt;br&gt;Title: Regional Vice President ASC Operations  &lt;br&gt;Location: Must live in North NJ, NY, or commutable to territory weekly  &lt;br&gt;Travel: Travel throughout NY up to 50% of the time &lt;br&gt;Be mindful of any non-compete issues and disclose this information  &lt;br&gt;Bonus: 40% of annual salary &lt;br&gt;# of Direct Reports: No direct reports, many in-direct reports at the centers and lots of department collaboration with corporate and clinical on Managed Service Organization side. &lt;br&gt;Extensive Details:  &lt;ol start="1"&gt;&lt;br&gt;Advanced degrees, MBA, MHA, or others are a plus &lt;br&gt;At least 5 years ' experience in a healthcare service operations role with a strong emphasis in strategic planning and financial performance management &lt;br&gt;Experience working and traveling to multiple sites (ideally in NY) &lt;br&gt;5+ years of working with healthcare providers in a leadership capacity.  &lt;br&gt;Experience managing relationships with physicians (owning physicians, board, medical directors, etc.) &lt;br&gt;Ideally, prior experience with single-specialty or multi-specialty Ambulatory Surgery Centers the following will also work&lt;br&gt;Practice, hospital, or OBS (office based surgery) - as long as more about strategic growth and not operations   &lt;br&gt;Ideally, for profit management experience in a managed service organization the following will also work&lt;br&gt;Large practice group or hospital joint venture setting where they focused primarily on the successful operations and growth of multiple locations.   &lt;br&gt;Strong understanding of financials and operations - ability to look at financial and operational deficiencies, see trouble coming and fix proactively. &lt;br&gt;Should have experience in Revenue Cycle/ Billing experience &lt;br&gt;Experience with mergers and acquisitions  -  we would love someone who has developed new business or been a part of that process.  &lt;br&gt;Experience with physician recruitment, organic growth succession planning, and patient access   &lt;br&gt;#DH</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Administrative Staff</Profession>
			<Specialty>Gastroenterology</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Jamison</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>PA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115536</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Permanent Physician - Geriatrics - Maryland - 115536</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;This opportunity offers a Monday through Friday, flexible hour, full-time schedule. &lt;br&gt;As part of a collaborative team consisting of Medical Director, Attending Physician and Nurse Practitioner, you will admit, round on and discharge short term rehab and long-term care patients at our partner Skilled Nursing Facilities.  &lt;br&gt;You will be responsible for history and physical exams and medical rounds.  &lt;br&gt;You will also provide cross coverage as needed by colleague medical staff; perform evaluations on patients with changes in condition and attend to patients as requested by facility staff; collaborate with Nurse Practitioners and maintain compliance with all facility quality initiatives. &lt;br&gt;Bread and Butter of Medicine and Acute and Post-Acute Care&lt;br&gt;Assigns MD' s locations that are within a 30 minute radius of their home location. Typically providers are rotating between 3-4 facilities maximum. &lt;br&gt;Geriatrics, Internal Medicine &amp; Primary Care  - Long Term Care/Geriatric Population. Geriatric care experience and Acute Care Experience a MUST. &lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;The &amp;ldquo; helpful to have&amp;rdquo; vs &amp;ldquo; must have&amp;rdquo;&lt;br&gt;Wide and deep understanding of Medicine  -  must &lt;br&gt;LTC experience  -  helpful &lt;br&gt;Acute/subacute care experience  -  helpful &lt;br&gt;Hospitalist experience with certain skills like cath placements, bed sore treatment etc.  -  helpful and expanded upon the fact that they they ' ve had a few hospitalists come over to them, which have worked out well, but said they did have to re-wire them a bit, but that training is possible. &lt;br&gt;If their experience in a LTC facility was during residency...Is that something you will consider? Yes &lt;br&gt;Relocation assistance available  &lt;br&gt;#DH</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Geriatrics</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Linthicum Heights</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>MD</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115535</JobID>
			<JobTitle>permanent - Nurse Practitioner - Texas</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>The Nurse Practitioner is responsible for coordinated and comprehensive care of its members at designated skilled nursing facilities.  &lt;br&gt;The nurse practitioner works in collaboration with the member ' s primary care physician to deliver exception health care. The nurse practitioner is the medical liaison to the interdisciplinary staff and allied health providers and communicates effectively to assure seamless delivery of services.&lt;br&gt;As a key member of the clinical team in the skilled nursing facility, the nurse practitioner provides preventive care, diagnoses both acute and chronic illnesses, orders and interprets diagnostic tests, prescribes medications, refers to specialists as appropriate,   establishes a plan of care with short-term and long-term goals, and is a resource to members, families, and staff.    &lt;br&gt;ESSENTIAL RESPONSIBILITIES &lt;br&gt;Demonstrates both autonomy and proficiency in performance of comprehensive health assessments.  &lt;br&gt;Collaborates with member ' s primary care physician to create a care plan focused on prevention, early detection and timely intervention. &lt;br&gt;Adheres to standards of documentation and communication as directed by the Model of Care. &lt;br&gt;Observes the scope of practice in the state in which he or she is licensed and working in. &lt;br&gt;Communicates with physicians and family members during transitions of care.   &lt;br&gt;Effectively communicates with all members of the care team and facilitates a medically appropriate and effective plan of care to avoid unnecessary duplication of testing, and fragmentation of care. &lt;br&gt;Participates in case rounds to review skilled and hospitalized members.   &lt;br&gt;Performs duties as assigned.  &lt;br&gt;Requirements: &lt;br&gt;Minimum of 3 years clinical care experience. &lt;br&gt;Clinical competence and understanding of evidenced-based practice.      &lt;br&gt;Proficient in basic computer skills- confidence in learning and using unfamiliar computer programs and electronic devices.   &lt;br&gt;Strong commitment to the care of the elderly and the needs of their families &lt;br&gt;Solid interpersonal and communication skills &lt;br&gt;Good organizational skills &lt;br&gt;Admirable teaching skills &lt;br&gt;Strong customer service orientation &lt;br&gt;Skilled Nursing Facility/Long Term Care experience preferred. &lt;br&gt;Case management experience preferred &lt;br&gt;Knowledge of current standard medical practices and experience with Medicare/Medicaid. &lt;br&gt;Detailed knowledge of I-SNP MOC and I-SNP population. &lt;br&gt;Proficiency in nursing/medical databases and Microsoft programs. &lt;br&gt;Positive and enthusiastic attitud                                                                                                                 &lt;br&gt;LICENSURE, CREDENTIALING AND CERTIFICATION &lt;br&gt;Currently licensed as an Acute, Adult/Gerontological or Family Nurse Practitioner in the state of practice.  &lt;br&gt;Meets the Provider Partner Health Plan credentialing requirements.   &lt;br&gt;Holds or is eligible for DEA licensure and CDS licensure (if required in the state of practice) &lt;br&gt;Basic Cardiac Life Support certification.   &lt;br&gt;Current unrestricted RN license for the state in which the Nurse Care Coordinator is practicing.                                                                                                                                                 &lt;br&gt;We are an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, age, religion, gender, gender identity, sexual orientation, national origin, genetic information, veteran, or disability status.&lt;br&gt;#DH</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Nurse Practitioner</Profession>
			<Specialty>Registered Nurse</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Linthicum Heights</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>MD</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115532</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Permanent / W-2 | Registered Nurse - Maryland | 115532</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>The Nurse Practioner is responsible for coordinated and comprehensive care of its members at designated skilled nursing facilities.   The nurse practitioner works in collaboration with the member ' s primary care physician to deliver exception health care.  The nurse practitioner is the medical liaison to the interdisciplinary staff and allied health providers and communicates effectively to assure seamless delivery of services.&lt;br&gt;As a key member of the clinical team in the skilled nursing facility, the nurse practitioner provides preventive care, diagnoses both acute and chronic illnesses, orders and interprets diagnostic tests, prescribes medications, refers to specialists as appropriate,   establishes a plan of care with short-term and long-term goals, and is a resource to members, families, and staff.    &lt;br&gt;ESSENTIAL RESPONSIBILITIES &lt;br&gt;Demonstrates both autonomy and proficiency in performance of comprehensive health assessments.  &lt;br&gt;Collaborates with member ' s primary care physician to create a care plan focused on prevention, early detection and timely intervention. &lt;br&gt;Adheres to standards of documentation and communication. &lt;br&gt;Observes the scope of practice in the state in which he or she is licensed and working in. &lt;br&gt;Communicates with physicians and family members during transitions of care.   &lt;br&gt;Effectively communicates with all members of the care team and facilitates a medically appropriate and effective plan of care to avoid unnecessary duplication of testing, and fragmentation of care. &lt;br&gt;Participates in case rounds to review skilled and hospitalized members.   &lt;br&gt;Performs duties as assigned.  &lt;br&gt;Requirements: &lt;br&gt;Minimum of 3 years clinical care experience. &lt;br&gt;Clinical competence and understanding of evidenced-based practice.      &lt;br&gt;Proficient in basic computer skills- confidence in learning and using unfamiliar computer programs and electronic devices.   &lt;br&gt;Strong commitment to the care of the elderly and the needs of their families &lt;br&gt;Solid interpersonal and communication skills &lt;br&gt;Good organizational skills &lt;br&gt;Admirable teaching skills &lt;br&gt;Strong customer service orientation &lt;br&gt;Skilled Nursing Facility/Long Term Care experience preferred. &lt;br&gt;Case management experience preferred &lt;br&gt;Knowledge of current standard medical practices and experience with Medicare/Medicaid. &lt;br&gt;Detailed knowledge of I-SNP MOC and I-SNP population. &lt;br&gt;Proficiency in nursing/medical databases and Microsoft programs. &lt;br&gt;Positive and enthusiastic attitude                                                                                                                 &lt;br&gt;LICENSURE, CREDENTIALING AND CERTIFICATION &lt;br&gt;Currently licensed as an Acute, Adult/Gerontological or Family Nurse Practitioner in the state of practice.  &lt;br&gt;Meets the Provider Partner Health Plan credentialing requirements.   &lt;br&gt;Holds or is eligible for DEA licensure and CDS licensure (if required in the state of practice) &lt;br&gt;Basic Cardiac Life Support certification.   &lt;br&gt;Current unrestricted RN license for the state in which the Nurse Care Coordinator is practicing.                                                                                                                                                 &lt;br&gt;OTHER REQUIREMENTS&lt;br&gt;We are an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, age, religion, gender, gender identity, sexual orientation, national origin, genetic information, veteran, or disability status.&lt;br&gt;#DH</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Nurse Practitioner</Profession>
			<Specialty>Geriatrics</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Linthicum Heights</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>MD</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115531</JobID>
			<JobTitle>permanent - Nurse Practitioner - northern Illinois - 115531</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>The   Nurse Practitioner is responsible for coordinated and comprehensive care of its members at designated skilled nursing facilities.  &lt;br&gt;The nurse practitioner works in collaboration with the member ' s primary care physician to deliver exception health care. The nurse practitioner is the medical liaison to the interdisciplinary staff and allied health providers and communicates effectively to assure seamless delivery of services.&lt;br&gt;As a key member of the clinical team in the skilled nursing facility, the nurse practitioner provides preventive care, diagnoses both acute and chronic illnesses, orders and interprets diagnostic tests, prescribes medications, refers to specialists as appropriate,   establishes a plan of care with short-term and long-term goals, and is a resource to members, families, and staff.    &lt;br&gt;ESSENTIAL RESPONSIBILITIES &lt;br&gt;Demonstrates both autonomy and proficiency in performance of comprehensive health assessments.  &lt;br&gt;Collaborates with member ' s primary care physician to create a care plan focused on prevention, early detection and timely intervention. &lt;br&gt;Adheres to Provider Partners Health Plan standards of documentation and communication. &lt;br&gt;Observes the scope of practice in the state in which he or she is licensed and working in. &lt;br&gt;Communicates with physicians and family members during transitions of care.   &lt;br&gt;Effectively communicates with all members of the care team and facilitates a medically appropriate and effective plan of care to avoid unnecessary duplication of testing, and fragmentation of care. &lt;br&gt;Participates in case rounds to review skilled and hospitalized members.   &lt;br&gt;Performs duties as assigned.  &lt;br&gt;Experience &amp; Education: &lt;br&gt;Minimum of 3 years clinical care experience. &lt;br&gt;Clinical competence and understanding of evidenced-based practice.      &lt;br&gt;Proficient in basic computer skills- confidence in learning and using unfamiliar computer programs and electronic devices.   &lt;br&gt;Strong commitment to the care of the elderly and the needs of their families &lt;br&gt;Solid interpersonal and communication skills &lt;br&gt;Good organizational skills &lt;br&gt;Admirable teaching skills &lt;br&gt;Strong customer service orientation &lt;br&gt;Skilled Nursing Facility/Long Term Care experience preferred. &lt;br&gt;Case management experience preferred &lt;br&gt;Knowledge of current standard medical practices and experience with Medicare/Medicaid. &lt;br&gt;Detailed knowledge of I-SNP MOC and I-SNP population. &lt;br&gt;Proficiency in nursing/medical databases and Microsoft programs. &lt;br&gt;Positive and enthusiastic attitude                                                                                                           &lt;br&gt;LICENSURE, CREDENTIALING AND CERTIFICATION &lt;br&gt;Currently licensed as an Acute, Adult/Gerontological or Family Nurse Practitioner in the state of practice.  &lt;br&gt;Meets the Provider Partner Health Plan credentialing requirements.   &lt;br&gt;Holds or is eligible for DEA licensure and CDS licensure (if required in the state of practice) &lt;br&gt;Basic Cardiac Life Support certification.   &lt;br&gt;Current unrestricted RN license for the state in which the Nurse Care Coordinator is practicing.                                                                                                                                                 &lt;br&gt;OTHER REQUIREMENTS&lt;br&gt;We are an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, age, religion, gender, gender identity, sexual orientation, national origin, genetic information, veteran, or disability status.&lt;br&gt;#DH&lt;br&gt;</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Nurse Practitioner</Profession>
			<Specialty>Registered Nurse</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Linthicum Heights</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>MD</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115529</JobID>
			<JobTitle>RN Care Coordinator - northern Illinois - 115529</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>The Nurse Care Coordinator will play a key role in the execution of the Model of Care (MOC) through the collaborative process of assessment, planning, facilitation, care coordination, evaluation, and advocacy for options and services to meet the comprehensive health needs of each member of the program. Utilizing effective communication skills and available resources, the Nurse Care Coordinator will promote quality, cost-effective outcomes, including care coordination for complex and multiple chronic conditions of the long-term care resident.   Additional responsibilities include:&lt;br&gt;No Call &lt;br&gt;Case identification/risk stratification to establish needs of the PPHP member. &lt;br&gt;Collaboration with the Transitional Care Team to reduce re-admissions/avoid inappropriate hospitalizations. &lt;br&gt;Conducting and documenting a comprehensive assessment of barriers to care (medical, social, psychosocial, and literacy) promoting a holistic approach to developing the plan of care. &lt;br&gt;Coordinating integrated care plan development, including collaboration with nursing staff, leadership, as well as the entire interdisciplinary team. &lt;br&gt;Facilitation of developing appropriate referrals/consultations. &lt;br&gt;Documentation of care plans in the gEHRimed EMR &lt;br&gt;Outcomes management and evaluation of the achievement of established goals within the plan of care. &lt;br&gt;Ensures initial and annual follow up Model of Care training occurs for employees, providers and contracted personnel associated with ISNP program  Requirements:&lt;br&gt;Current unrestricted RN license for the state in which the Nurse Care Coordinator is practicing. &lt;br&gt;Minimum of 3 years clinical care experience. &lt;br&gt;  Skilled Nursing Facility/Long Term Care experience preferred. &lt;br&gt;Case management experience preferred &lt;br&gt;Strong nursing expertise in managing complex cases with minimal supervision. &lt;br&gt;Knowledge of current standard medical practices and experience with Medicare/Medicaid. &lt;br&gt;Ability to work with and communicate on a professional level with the interdisciplinary team. &lt;br&gt;Excellent independent critical thinking/problem-solving skills. &lt;br&gt;Detailed knowledge of I-SNP MOC and I-SNP population. &lt;br&gt;Excellent oral and written interpersonal communication, organizational, multi-tasking, and teamwork skills. &lt;br&gt;Proficiency in nursing/medical databases and Microsoft programs. &lt;br&gt;Positive and enthusiastic attitude. &lt;br&gt;Valid driver ' s license and car insurance with reliable transportation  &lt;br&gt;#DH</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Registered Nurse</Profession>
			<Specialty>Registered Nurse</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Linthicum Heights</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>MD</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115509</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Fulltime/W2 CRNAs - outside of Waco, Texas - plenty of OT - 115509</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Fulltime/W2 CRNAs - central Texas - plenty of OT - 115509 &lt;br&gt;Specialty: multiple fulltime/W2 CRNAs needed &lt;br&gt;Cases: Limited OB, No regional Neuro Block, No peripherals &lt;br&gt;Salary: Competitive &lt;br&gt;Overtime: plentiful &lt;br&gt;Flexible Schedule: 8, 10, 12 or 13 hour shifts &lt;br&gt;Weekday call:  1x per month. &lt;br&gt;Benefits: 401k, Medical, Dental, Vision&lt;br&gt;relocation assistance (as needed) &lt;br&gt;PTO &lt;br&gt;No State income Tax &lt;br&gt;sign on bonus   &lt;br&gt;Notes: Quick interview process! This is a well-respected health system! &lt;br&gt;State: Texas   &lt;br&gt;#DH</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Certified Registered Nurse Ane</Profession>
			<Specialty>Anesthesia General</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>central</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>TX</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115479</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Fulltime/W2 Emergency Medicine Physician Opportunity in Southern Oregon - 115479</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Fulltime/W2 Emergency Medicine Physician Opportunity in Southern Oregon - 115479 &lt;br&gt;Candidates must be BC/BE in Emergency Medicine (ABEM) &lt;br&gt;Site: Level III trauma center &lt;br&gt;Competitive hourly rate &lt;br&gt;Annual performance incentives &lt;br&gt;Evening shift differential &lt;br&gt;Signing bonus &lt;br&gt;Relocation assistance &lt;br&gt;Annual CME allowance &lt;br&gt;Generous time off accrual plan &lt;br&gt;Excellent health, dental, vision, and retirement benefits &lt;br&gt;State: Oregon &lt;br&gt;Job Number: 115479  &lt;br&gt;#DH</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Emergency Medicine</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Medford</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115417</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time W2 Director of Anesthesia (Anesthesiologist) is Needed in Manhattan (NY) - 115417</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Full-time W2 Director of Anesthesia (Anesthesiologist) is Needed in Manhattan (NY) - 115417 &lt;br&gt;Position type:  Anesthesiologist &lt;br&gt;Types of cases:  EGD, CS, Flex Sig, HET   &lt;br&gt;Board Certified or Board Eligibility status:  Board Certified  &lt;br&gt;Exact hours, any evenings or weekends expected:  M-F First cases start roughly 7: 00a last case start avg. 4: 00p/4: 30p.  &lt;br&gt;Benefits: .M/d/v/p offered; paid holidays and additional perks and coverage &lt;br&gt;State: New York &lt;br&gt;Job Number:  115417  &lt;br&gt;#DH</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Anesthesia General</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Jamison</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>PA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115239</JobID>
			<JobTitle>permanent - Operating Room Manager - Pennsylvania - 115239</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;Primary Function:&lt;br&gt;Under the direction of the Director of Perioperative services the Operating Room manager is responsible for coordinating all nursing care and related activities of the Operating Room in coordination with Pre-Op and PACU managers, Material Management, and Central Processing to deliver high quality patient outcomes. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Essential Duties: &lt;br&gt;Performs essential duties in accordance with established standards of Perioperative Nursing practice. &lt;br&gt;Collaborates with staff, physicians and other hospital leaders to ensure patient needs are met and quality out comes are achieved. &lt;br&gt;Ensure the staff is adhering to Hospital policies and procedures &lt;br&gt;Identifies the need to evaluate and revise nursing policies and procedures as changes occur in the perioperative arena. &lt;br&gt;Participates in quality improvement programs and initiatives. &lt;br&gt;Conducts and attends weekly staff meetings and in-services in collaboration with the Nurse Educator. &lt;br&gt;Promotes cost effectiveness within the department through the management of time and resources. &lt;br&gt;Demonstrates adaptability, flexibility, and accountability when necessary changes are made to the job description. &lt;br&gt;Maintains appropriate certifications and professional organization memberships. &lt;br&gt;They see 45 to 50 cases day and can add up to 10-12 if needed. They do general surgery and have robotics, a heart room, ortho room and robotics.  &lt;br&gt;EMR is EPIC    &lt;br&gt;Qualifications: &lt;br&gt;Education &amp; Training: &lt;br&gt;BSN required, MSN preferred &lt;br&gt;CNOR preferred and required within 1 year   &lt;br&gt;Experience: &lt;br&gt;5 years clinical experience in the Operating Room &lt;br&gt;2 years' experience in Leadership/Management   &lt;br&gt;License, Certification &amp; Registration: &lt;br&gt;Current licensure as a Registered Nurse in the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania required &lt;br&gt;BLS Certification through American Heart Association required  &lt;br&gt;ACLS &amp; PALS certification through American Heart Association preferred  &lt;br&gt;Full Time / 40 hours weekly  -  5 days a week / 8am-4: 30pm &lt;br&gt;No on call requirements &lt;br&gt;The salary is based on a variety of factors: &lt;br&gt;Years of RN exp, &lt;br&gt;Years of Nurse Manager exp, &lt;br&gt;Education  &lt;br&gt;Leadership Certifications &lt;br&gt;# of direct reports (TBD) - Typically 130   &lt;br&gt;Everyone is eligible for the same annual increases based on performance &lt;br&gt;There is a Manager Incentive Plan (Bonus): Payment is based on a combination of individual goal achievement and organization goal achievement (candidate can discuss in more detail during the interview)  &lt;br&gt;#DH</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>General Surgery</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Philadelphia</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>PA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114618</JobID>
			<JobTitle>W2 Hospitalist Opportunity in beautiful southern Oregon - 114618</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>W2 Hospitalist Opportunity in beautiful southern Oregon - 114618 &lt;br&gt;This is a full-time position with flexible block scheduling &lt;br&gt;Candidates must be BC/BE in Internal Medicine &lt;br&gt;level III Trauma Center &lt;br&gt;Competitive pay with incentives, sign-on bonus, relocation assistance, and excellent benefits &lt;br&gt;State: Oregon &lt;br&gt;Job number: 114618  &lt;br&gt;#DH</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Hospitalist</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Medford</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114636</JobID>
			<JobTitle>3 W2 Radiologists Needed in New Jersey ASAP! - 114636</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Needs: RadiologistsX 1 MammographerX 2 Body Imager &lt;br&gt;Competitive salary &lt;br&gt;Highlights&lt;br&gt;Full-time positions  &lt;br&gt;No night shifts required.  &lt;br&gt;Teaching opportunities with residents and medical students &lt;br&gt;Emphasis on patient experience, quality and safety &lt;br&gt;Home workstations supplied &lt;br&gt;Secure employment with low physician turnover &lt;br&gt;Potential for career advancement in administrative, utilization review, quality or educational roles &lt;br&gt;On-site parking  &lt;br&gt;#DH</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Radiology</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Camden</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>NJ</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114622</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Neurology MD Opportunity for W2/Fulltime Candidates! - Southern Oregon - 114622</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Neurology MD Opportunity for W2/Fulltime Candidates! - Southern Oregon - 114622 &lt;br&gt;Specialty: General neurologist; must be BC/BE &lt;br&gt;Primarily outpatient with a small amount of inpatient practice &lt;br&gt;Competitive base salary &lt;br&gt;Annual incentives &lt;br&gt;Sign-on bonus &lt;br&gt;Relocation assistance &lt;br&gt;Fantastic PTO &lt;br&gt;Excellent healthcare benefits &lt;br&gt;State: Oregon &lt;br&gt;Job Number: 114622  &lt;br&gt;#DH</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Neurology Adult</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Medford</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114620</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Fulltime/W2 Endocrinology PA Needed in Southern Oregon - 114620</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Fulltime/W2 Endocrinology PA Needed in Southern Oregon - 114620 &lt;br&gt;Environment: Collaborative team &lt;br&gt;Competitive salary &lt;br&gt;Sign-on bonus &lt;br&gt;Relocation assistance &lt;br&gt;Great PTO &lt;br&gt;Excellent healthcare benefits &lt;br&gt;State: Oregon &lt;br&gt;Job Number: 114620  &lt;br&gt;#RPO</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician Assistant</Profession>
			<Specialty>Endocrinology</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Medford</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114621</JobID>
			<JobTitle>W2 General Neuro NP/PA Opportunity in Southern Oregon! - 114621</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>General Neuro NP Opportunity in Southern Oregon! - 114621 &lt;br&gt;100% outpatient role &lt;br&gt;competitive base salary + incentives &lt;br&gt;sign-on bonus &lt;br&gt;Relocation assistance &lt;br&gt;great PTO &lt;br&gt;Excellent healthcare benefits &lt;br&gt;State: Oregon &lt;br&gt;Job Number: 114621  &lt;br&gt;#DH</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Neurology Adult</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Medford</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114617</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Fulltime/W2 primary care NP/PA opportunity in stunning southern Oregon (OR) - 114617</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Fulltime/W2 primary care NP/PA opportunity in stunning southern Oregon (OR) - 114617 &lt;br&gt;Schedule/Shifts: flexible scheduling options, no call or inpatient work required &lt;br&gt;Compensation: competitive, great incentives, sign-on bonus, relocation assistance, great PTO and benefits &lt;br&gt;State: Oregon &lt;br&gt;Job Number: 114617  &lt;br&gt;#DH</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Primary Care (FM/IM)</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Medford</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114615</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Permanent Primary Care (FM/IM) Primary Care Opportunity in Southern Oregon! - 114615</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Primary Care (FM/IM) Primary Care Opportunity in Southern Oregon! - 114615 &lt;br&gt;Outpatient only &lt;br&gt;Candidates must be BC/BE in Family or Internal Medicine.  &lt;br&gt;Schedule/Shifts: flexible scheduling options, no call or inpatient work required &lt;br&gt;Pay: Competitive compensation with incentives, sign-on bonus, relocation assistance, and great benefits and PTO &lt;br&gt;State: Oregon &lt;br&gt;Job Number: 114615  &lt;br&gt;#DH</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Primary Care (FM/IM)</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Medford</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>113095</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time Telepsychiatry, Consult-Liaison Position: Great Benefits, Awesome People &amp; Work-life Balance - 113095</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>We are looking for Psychiatrists who are passionate about telehealth and bringing care to the patient to keep them in their community. Clinicians working in our consult liaison staffing pods will work with a variety of hospitals and health systems doing everything from ED consults to floor consults and follow-ups. This group of highly engaged clinicians will get exposure to a variety of patient populations in different states across the country. &lt;br&gt;100% Remote Telepsychiatry &lt;br&gt;Ages: All Ages &lt;br&gt;Any State License Accepted &lt;br&gt;Will Pay for Additional Licensing &lt;br&gt;Various Shifts (Day/Evening/Night/Weekend) &lt;br&gt;Fast hiring process &lt;br&gt;High Earning Potential &lt;br&gt;Healthcare, Dental and Vision Insurance for you and your family -401k Plan  &lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;Completion of a 4-year ACGME Residency Program in Psychiatry &lt;br&gt;Must be Board Certified or truly Board Eligible (within 5 years of residency) &lt;br&gt;2 Years of consult-liaison psychiatry experience  &lt;br&gt;We look forward to hearing from you!&lt;br&gt;Contact: Gary Lazarusgary.Lazarus@iconmn.Com(971) 381-5352&lt;br&gt;#DH</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Psychiatry Adult</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Herndon</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>VA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114040</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Permanent Anesthesiologists Needed in the Greater Philadelphia Area (PA) - 114040</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;Perm Anesthesiologists Needed in the Greater Philadelphia Area - 114040&lt;br&gt;Specialties:&lt;br&gt;2 Pediatric, 2 Cardiology,   8 General Anesthesiologists&lt;br&gt;Compensation: &lt;br&gt;Competitive Salary &lt;br&gt;Sign-on Bonus &lt;br&gt;Relocation assistance  &lt;br&gt;Benefits &amp; Perks: &lt;br&gt;Highly Competitive compensation with a superb benefits package &lt;br&gt;Variety of site, specialty, and schedule  &lt;br&gt;Low-cost health insurance for employees and their families &lt;br&gt;Generous CME allowance &lt;br&gt;Top-tier retirement programs &lt;br&gt;Malpractice Insurance with Tail Coverage  &lt;br&gt;Relocation Assistance   &lt;br&gt;Practice /Position Overview:  &lt;br&gt;Seeking anesthesiologists with a variety of clinical interests and expertise, with emphasis on general and orthopedic anesthesia, cardiovascular anesthesia, pediatric anesthesia, obstetric anesthesia, and neuroanesthesia, as our network continues to grow and add to the scale and clinical specialization of the care we deliver. &lt;br&gt;Opportunities for diverse practice experience of case and facility type, or focused practice geographically or clinically. &lt;br&gt;Opportunities for facility and subspecialty leadership and professional development. An opportunity to explore clinical research is available and will be supported.  &lt;br&gt;Job Qualifications:&lt;br&gt;Passion for clinical work to positively impact patient care, safety, and experience. &lt;br&gt;Must be Board Eligible or Board Certified with the American Board of Anesthesiology &lt;br&gt;A valid Pennsylvania Medical License or the ability to obtain one is required  &lt;br&gt;Influenza vaccination and COVID-19 Vaccination is required for all colleagues unless medically contraindicated or due to a bona fide religious belief or practice. Applicants possessing a medical marijuana card will not be considered for safety-sensitive positions.EOE.&lt;br&gt;#DH&lt;br&gt;</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Anesthesia General</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Allentown</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>PA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>112784</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Hospitalist - 112784</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;Shift Times: Day (7am-7pm), Swing 4pm-4am), Night (7pm-7am), Admitter MD: (8: 30am-8: 30p &lt;br&gt;Per Day: Day Providers: 4, 4 Rounders/1 admitter, 1 Swing Provider, 1 Night Provider &lt;br&gt;No call schedule &lt;br&gt;Average Daily Admits: 7-10  &lt;br&gt;Lead MD: point of contact early AM admits (prior to 830am Admitter start time); attends Codes/RRTs, assists with consults as needed &lt;br&gt;Swing: primarily admitting position/crosscovers hospital with nocturnist &lt;br&gt;APP: practices independently in Oregon; carries 14-16 patients  </JobDescription>
			<Profession>Nurse Practitioner</Profession>
			<Specialty>Hospitalist</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Springfield</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>Emma.Blades@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>112721</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Radiologist needed ASAP in California! - 112721</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Radiologist needed ASAP in California! &lt;br&gt;Great Rate &lt;br&gt;travel and lodging covered &lt;br&gt;Start: August 1, 2022 &lt;br&gt;Work schedule: 8a-5p &lt;br&gt;No call  &lt;br&gt;Patients per day:  85 reads a day for whole facility. 30 CT, 20 Ultrasound, 30-40 Diagnostic.   </JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Radiology Diagnostic</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Santa Cruz</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>CA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>caleb@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>112779</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Hospitalist - 112779</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;Dates: 8/26/22 (ongoing) &lt;br&gt;LOA: Monday Oct 17th - Sunday Oct 23rd, Monday Oct 31st - Sunday Nov 6th &lt;br&gt;Ongoing through Jan/Feb 2023 &lt;br&gt;Schedule: 7am - 7pm &lt;br&gt;No call schedule &lt;br&gt;Inpatient (10 pt per day) &lt;br&gt;Staff: MD &amp; Support staff  </JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Hospitalist</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Berlin</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>NH</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>Emma.Blades@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>112481</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Primary Care (FM/IM) - 112481</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;Start: As soon as credentialed &lt;br&gt;Schedule: Monday - Thursday (7am - 5pm) &lt;br&gt;Outpatient (25-28 PPD)  </JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Primary Care (FM/IM)</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Sacramento</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>CA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>caleb@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>112720</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Emergency Medicine Physician Needed ASAP in Ohio! - 112720</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription> Emergency Medicine Physician Needed ASAP in Ohio!  &lt;br&gt;Great rate! &lt;br&gt;Will cover travel and lodging   &lt;br&gt;Duration: ASAP for 10-12 shifts a month (12 hour shifts) &lt;br&gt;no call &lt;br&gt;case types: ER  </JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Emergency Medicine</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Oakdale</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>CA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>caleb@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>112719</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Emergency Medicine Physician Needed in California - 112719</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;great rate! &lt;br&gt;travel and lodging covered &lt;br&gt;Does the Provider need to prescribe?  Yes &lt;br&gt;Duration: ASAP for 12-15 shifts/month (12 hour shifts) &lt;br&gt;no call &lt;br&gt;case types: ER   &lt;br&gt;</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Emergency Medicine</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Hollister</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>CA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>caleb@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>112677</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Emergency Medicine - 112677</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;Start: ASAP post credentialing Provider works with scheduler to book dates 2 months in advance General acute care hospital with 24 hours of physician coverage daily in 11 and 13-hour shifts No call schedule Emergency Room  </JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Emergency Medicine</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Healdsburg</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>CA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>caleb@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>112663</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Urgent Care - 112663</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;Dates: 9/12/22 8/1/2023 &lt;br&gt;LOA: 4(10 HR) shifts  -  6 -  12-month contract &lt;br&gt;Schedule: Clinic is open 9A-10P  -  flexibility in shift times but must commit to 4 (10HR) shifts per week, including two weekend days per month &lt;br&gt;No call schedule &lt;br&gt;Outpatient (2.5 patients per hour)  </JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Urgent Care</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Portland</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>Emma.Blades@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>112563</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Family Medicine - 112563</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;Start: ASAC &lt;br&gt;Full time with flexible scheduling &lt;br&gt;Minimal Call (1: 5) &lt;br&gt;Outpatient &lt;br&gt;Staff:  Dedicated support staff. On-site Integrated Behaviorist and laboratory services  </JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Family Medicine</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Corvallis</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>Emma.Blades@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>112446</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Radiology Diagnostic - 112446</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;Schedule: Monday - Friday &lt;br&gt;Hours: 8am - 5pm &lt;br&gt;No call schedule/weekends &lt;br&gt;Reads: 80-100 a day &lt;br&gt;Specific Reads: Mostly diagnostic, MRI reads needed  </JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Radiology Diagnostic</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Northern</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>NY</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>caleb@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>112403</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Outpatient Psychiatrist Permanent Position in an amazing Oregon location - 112403</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;PERM Outpatient Psychiatrist APP &lt;br&gt;Adult inpatient and outpatient Behavioral Health services  </JobDescription>
			<Profession>Advanced Practice Providers</Profession>
			<Specialty>Psychiatry</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Medford</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>Emma.Blades@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>112402</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Permanent Positions Available for both NPs and PAs in beautiful Oregon - 112402</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;Perm Pulmonary/Critical Care NP/PA &lt;br&gt;Shift: Variable Hours/Variable Days (full time)  </JobDescription>
			<Profession>Nurse Practitioner</Profession>
			<Specialty>Pulmonology Critical Care</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Medford</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>Emma.Blades@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
	</jobs>
</File>
