<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
	<jobs>
		<job>
			<JobID>113095</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time Telepsychiatry, Consult-Liaison Position: Great Benefits, Awesome People &amp; Work-life Balance - 113095</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>We are looking for Psychiatrists who are passionate about telehealth and bringing care to the patient to keep them in their community. Clinicians working in our consult liaison staffing pods will work with a variety of hospitals and health systems doing everything from ED consults to floor consults and follow-ups. This group of highly engaged clinicians will get exposure to a variety of patient populations in different states across the country. &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
100% Remote Telepsychiatry&lt;br&gt;
Ages: All Ages&lt;br&gt;
Any State License Accepted&lt;br&gt;
Will Pay for Additional Licensing&lt;br&gt;
Various Shifts (Day/Evening/Night/Weekend)&lt;br&gt;
Fast hiring process&lt;br&gt;
High Earning Potential&lt;br&gt;
Healthcare, Dental and Vision Insurance for you and your family -401k Plan&lt;br&gt;
 Qualifications: &lt;br&gt;
Completion of a 4-year ACGME Residency Program in Psychiatry&lt;br&gt;
Must be Board Certified or truly Board Eligible (within 5 years of residency)&lt;br&gt;
2 Years of consult-liaison psychiatry experience&lt;br&gt;
 We look forward to hearing from you! Contact: Gary Lazarus gary.lazarus@iconmn.com (971) 381-5352 </JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Psychiatry Adult</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Herndon</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>VA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115509</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Fulltime/W2 CRNAs - outside of Waco, Texas - plenty of OT - 115509</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Fulltime/W2 CRNAs - outside of Waco, Texas - plenty of OT - 115509 &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
Specialty: multiple fulltime/W2 CRNAs needed&lt;br&gt;
Cases: Limited OB, No regional Neuro Block, No peripherals&lt;br&gt;
Salary: Competitive&lt;br&gt;
Overtime: plentiful&lt;br&gt;
Flexible Schedule: 8, 10, 12 or 13 hour shifts&lt;br&gt;
Weekday call: 1x per month.&lt;br&gt;
Benefits:401k, Medical, Dental, Vision&lt;br&gt;
relocation assistance (as needed)&lt;br&gt;
PTO&lt;br&gt;
No State income Tax&lt;br&gt;
sign on bonus&lt;br&gt;
Notes: Quick interview process! This is a well-respected health system!&lt;br&gt;
State: Texas</JobDescription>
			<Profession>CRNA</Profession>
			<Specialty>Anesthesia General</Specialty>
			<SiteState>TX</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115513</JobID>
			<JobTitle>W2 CRNA positions open in TX - 115513</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>WILL GET MORE DETAILS.  Michelle is the lead and client facing.  &lt;br&gt;
 Baylor Scott &amp;amp; White &lt;br&gt;
 Hospital: BAYLOR SCOTT &amp;amp; WHITE MEDICAL CENTER  -  TEMPLE - 2401 S  31ST ST, Temple, TX 76508 (Level 1 Trauma Center) &lt;br&gt;
 Client needs 14-20 FTE (CRNA) Would appreciate candidates with a wide range of exp (General, Otho, GI, etc.&amp;hellip;) ACT Model: Limited OB, No regional Neuro Block, No peripherals 33 Operating Rooms, 2 reserve. &lt;br&gt;
 Salary range is $180k (New Grad), $210  (5 years exp) and up&amp;hellip; Overtime is plentiful and can allow for a great increase in pay - $140/ hr. for Weekday and $160 / hour Weekend. &lt;br&gt;
 Flexible Schedule: 8, 10, 12 or 13 hour shifts Weekday call is 1x per month. &lt;br&gt;
 Benefits- 401k, Medical, Dental Vision  7k relocation assistance (as needed)  $4000 CME + 5 days of CME 5 Weeks PTO No State income Tax $100k sign on bonus  (50k after 30 days, 25k at the start of candidate's 2nd year and the remaining 25k at the start of year 3) Fully Funded MHA &lt;br&gt;
 Interview process will move fast  -  Prompt name clear then a 24 - 48-hour response to set up interview set up. Will meet regional and local CRNA leadership.  &lt;br&gt;
 Well respected health system  &lt;br&gt;
 </JobDescription>
			<Profession>CRNA</Profession>
			<Specialty>Anesthesia General</Specialty>
			<SiteState>TX</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115531</JobID>
			<JobTitle>permanent - Nurse Practitioner - northern Illinois - 115531</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>The  Nurse Practitioner is responsible for coordinated and comprehensive care of its members at designated skilled nursing facilities.   &lt;br&gt;
 The nurse practitioner works in collaboration with the member's primary care physician to deliver exception health care. The nurse practitioner is the medical liaison to the interdisciplinary staff and allied health providers and communicates effectively to assure seamless delivery of services. &lt;br&gt;
 As a key member of the clinical team in the skilled nursing facility, the nurse practitioner provides preventive care, diagnoses both acute and chronic illnesses, orders and interprets diagnostic tests, prescribes medications, refers to specialists as appropriate,  establishes a plan of care with short-term and long-term goals, and is a resource to members, families, and staff.     &lt;br&gt;
 ESSENTIAL RESPONSIBILITIES &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;ol&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Demonstrates both autonomy and proficiency in performance of comprehensive health assessments. &lt;br&gt;
Collaborates with member's primary care physician to create a care plan focused on prevention, early detection and timely intervention.&lt;br&gt;
Adheres to Provider Partners Health Plan standards of documentation and communication.&lt;br&gt;
Observes the scope of practice in the state in which he or she is licensed and working in.&lt;br&gt;
Communicates with physicians and family members during transitions of care.  &lt;br&gt;
Effectively communicates with all members of the care team and facilitates a medically appropriate and effective plan of care to avoid unnecessary duplication of testing, and fragmentation of care.&lt;br&gt;
Participates in case rounds to review skilled and hospitalized members.  &lt;br&gt;
Performs duties as assigned.&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 Experience &amp;amp; Education: &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
Minimum of 3 years clinical care experience.&lt;br&gt;
Clinical competence and understanding of evidenced-based practice.     &lt;br&gt;
Proficient in basic computer skills- confidence in learning and using unfamiliar computer programs and electronic devices.  &lt;br&gt;
Strong commitment to the care of the elderly and the needs of their families&lt;br&gt;
Solid interpersonal and communication skills&lt;br&gt;
Good organizational skills&lt;br&gt;
Admirable teaching skills&lt;br&gt;
Strong customer service orientation&lt;br&gt;
Skilled Nursing Facility/Long Term Care experience preferred.&lt;br&gt;
Case management experience preferred&lt;br&gt;
Knowledge of current standard medical practices and experience with Medicare/Medicaid.&lt;br&gt;
Detailed knowledge of I-SNP MOC and I-SNP population.&lt;br&gt;
Proficiency in nursing/medical databases and Microsoft programs.&lt;br&gt;
Positive and enthusiastic attitude                                                                                                         &lt;br&gt;
 LICENSURE, CREDENTIALING AND CERTIFICATION &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
Currently licensed as an Acute, Adult/Gerontological or Family Nurse Practitioner in the state of practice. &lt;br&gt;
Meets the Provider Partner Health Plan credentialing requirements.  &lt;br&gt;
Holds or is eligible for DEA licensure and CDS licensure (if required in the state of practice)&lt;br&gt;
Basic Cardiac Life Support certification.  &lt;br&gt;
Current unrestricted RN license for the state in which the Nurse Care Coordinator is practicing.                                                                                                                                               &lt;br&gt;
 OTHER REQUIREMENTS &lt;br&gt;
 We are an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, age, religion, gender, gender identity, sexual orientation, national origin, genetic information, veteran, or disability status. &lt;div align="center"&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 </JobDescription>
			<Profession>Nurse Practitioner</Profession>
			<Specialty>Registered Nurse</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Linthicum Heights</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>MD</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115532</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Permanent / W-2 | Registered Nurse - Maryland | 115532</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>The Nurse Practioner is responsible for coordinated and comprehensive care of its members at designated skilled nursing facilities.   The nurse practitioner works in collaboration with the member's primary care physician to deliver exception health care.  The nurse practitioner is the medical liaison to the interdisciplinary staff and allied health providers and communicates effectively to assure seamless delivery of services. &lt;br&gt;
 As a key member of the clinical team in the skilled nursing facility, the nurse practitioner provides preventive care, diagnoses both acute and chronic illnesses, orders and interprets diagnostic tests, prescribes medications, refers to specialists as appropriate,  establishes a plan of care with short-term and long-term goals, and is a resource to members, families, and staff.     &lt;br&gt;
 ESSENTIAL RESPONSIBILITIES &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;ol&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Demonstrates both autonomy and proficiency in performance of comprehensive health assessments. &lt;br&gt;
Collaborates with member's primary care physician to create a care plan focused on prevention, early detection and timely intervention.&lt;br&gt;
Adheres to standards of documentation and communication.&lt;br&gt;
Observes the scope of practice in the state in which he or she is licensed and working in.&lt;br&gt;
Communicates with physicians and family members during transitions of care.  &lt;br&gt;
Effectively communicates with all members of the care team and facilitates a medically appropriate and effective plan of care to avoid unnecessary duplication of testing, and fragmentation of care.&lt;br&gt;
Participates in case rounds to review skilled and hospitalized members.  &lt;br&gt;
Performs duties as assigned.&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/h4&gt;Requirements:  &lt;br&gt;
Minimum of 3 years clinical care experience.&lt;br&gt;
Clinical competence and understanding of evidenced-based practice.     &lt;br&gt;
Proficient in basic computer skills- confidence in learning and using unfamiliar computer programs and electronic devices.  &lt;br&gt;
Strong commitment to the care of the elderly and the needs of their families&lt;br&gt;
Solid interpersonal and communication skills&lt;br&gt;
Good organizational skills&lt;br&gt;
Admirable teaching skills&lt;br&gt;
Strong customer service orientation&lt;br&gt;
Skilled Nursing Facility/Long Term Care experience preferred.&lt;br&gt;
Case management experience preferred&lt;br&gt;
Knowledge of current standard medical practices and experience with Medicare/Medicaid.&lt;br&gt;
Detailed knowledge of I-SNP MOC and I-SNP population.&lt;br&gt;
Proficiency in nursing/medical databases and Microsoft programs.&lt;br&gt;
Positive and enthusiastic attitude                                                                                                               &lt;br&gt;
 LICENSURE, CREDENTIALING AND CERTIFICATION &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
Currently licensed as an Acute, Adult/Gerontological or Family Nurse Practitioner in the state of practice. &lt;br&gt;
Meets the Provider Partner Health Plan credentialing requirements.  &lt;br&gt;
Holds or is eligible for DEA licensure and CDS licensure (if required in the state of practice)&lt;br&gt;
Basic Cardiac Life Support certification.  &lt;br&gt;
Current unrestricted RN license for the state in which the Nurse Care Coordinator is practicing.                                                                                                                                               &lt;br&gt;
 OTHER REQUIREMENTS &lt;br&gt;
 We are an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, age, religion, gender, gender identity, sexual orientation, national origin, genetic information, veteran, or disability status. &lt;br&gt;
 </JobDescription>
			<Profession>Nurse Practitioner</Profession>
			<Specialty>Geriatrics</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Linthicum Heights</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>MD</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115536</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Permanent Physician - Geriatrics  - Maryland - 115536</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;
This opportunity offers a Monday through Friday, flexible hour, full-time schedule.&lt;br&gt;
As part of a collaborative team consisting of Medical Director, Attending Physician and Nurse Practitioner, you will admit, round on and discharge short term rehab and long-term care patients at our partner Skilled Nursing Facilities. &lt;br&gt;
You will be responsible for history and physical exams and medical rounds. &lt;br&gt;
You will also provide cross coverage as needed by colleague medical staff; perform evaluations on patients with changes in condition and attend to patients as requested by facility staff; collaborate with Nurse Practitioners and maintain compliance with all facility quality initiatives.&lt;br&gt;
Bread and Butter of Medicine and Acute and Post-Acute Care&lt;br&gt;
Assigns MD&amp;#39;s locations that are within a 30 minute radius of their home location. Typically providers are rotating between 3-4 facilities maximum.&lt;br&gt;
Geriatrics, Internal Medicine &amp;amp; Primary Care  - Long Term Care/Geriatric Population. Geriatric care experience and Acute Care Experience a MUST. &lt;br&gt;
 The "helpful to have" vs "must have" &lt;br&gt;
Wide and deep understanding of Medicine  -  must&lt;br&gt;
LTC experience  -  helpful&lt;br&gt;
Acute/subacute care experience  -  helpful&lt;br&gt;
Hospitalist experience with certain skills like cath placements, bed sore treatment etc.  -  helpful and expanded upon the fact that they they've had a few hospitalists come over to them, which have worked out well, but said they did have to re-wire them a bit, but that training is possible.&lt;br&gt;
If their experience in a LTC facility was during residency...is that something you will consider? Yes&lt;br&gt;
Relocation assistance available</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Geriatrics</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Linthicum Heights</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>MD</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115948</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-Time, Permanent Urology Position in Southwest NM</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Seeking full-time Urologist to join a part-time Urologist with anticipation of retirement in the next 12 months. &lt;br&gt;
 Position Highlights: &lt;br&gt;
Good General Surgery support and medical specialties support&lt;br&gt;
Very competitive compensation&lt;br&gt;
Paid malpractice insurance, DEA, controlled substance, and society dues&lt;br&gt;
Sign-on bonus, 401K, PTO&lt;br&gt;
Strong work/life balance&lt;br&gt;
Paid CME&lt;br&gt;
Community-run facility with 39 beds&lt;br&gt;
Good payor mix and strong community support&lt;br&gt;
 Surgeries include but are not limited to: &lt;br&gt;
Circumcision&lt;br&gt;
Vasectomy&lt;br&gt;
Cystoscopy&lt;br&gt;
Ureteroscopy for stone with and without stent placement&lt;br&gt;
EHWL Shock Wave Lithotripsy with and without Cystoscopy&lt;br&gt;
TURP with either resectoscope or laser&lt;br&gt;
Prostate biopsy&lt;br&gt;
Suprapubic Prostatectomy&lt;br&gt;
Radical Prostatectomy&lt;br&gt;
Nephrectomy&lt;br&gt;
Hydrocelectomy&lt;br&gt;
Varicocelectomy&lt;br&gt;
Orchiectomy, Orchiopexy&lt;br&gt;
 Location Highlights:  &lt;br&gt;
Rural Southeast New Mexico, adjacent to the West Texas border.&lt;br&gt;
One of New Mexico's best-kept secrets, we are located in southeastern New Mexico, nestled between the two larger cities. &lt;br&gt;
Our town offers a great school system, a small-town atmosphere, and tons of activities and something fun for every age.</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Urology</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Artesia</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>NM</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115950</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time, Permanent Non-Invasive Cardiology Job in New Mexico</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Seeking a Non-Invasive Cardiologist for an opening at a hospital in New Mexico. &lt;br&gt;
 Position Highlights: &lt;br&gt;
Non-Invasive Cardiology&lt;br&gt;
4.5 days of OP clinic and .5 administrative work&lt;br&gt;
Occasional Inpatient consult&lt;br&gt;
18 - 22 patients per day&lt;br&gt;
10 days of call a month (including 1 weekend)&lt;br&gt;
Procedures&lt;br&gt;
EKG and Holter interpretation&lt;br&gt;
Echo interpretation&lt;br&gt;
Treadmill and Chemical Stress Testing&lt;br&gt;
No Cardiac Catheterizations&lt;br&gt;
Board Certification not required but preferred&lt;br&gt;
Visa sponsorship available &lt;br&gt;
Sign-on offered&lt;br&gt;
 Hospital Details: &lt;br&gt;
39-bed, non-profit hospital&lt;br&gt;
Professional development opportunities&lt;br&gt;
Tuition reimbursement program&lt;br&gt;
Continuing education and clinical resources&lt;br&gt;
Benefits: 401K, healthcare insurance, life insurance and much more&lt;br&gt;
Other benefits may include Sign-on bonus, relocation assistance and CME allowance&lt;br&gt;
 Location Highlights:  &lt;br&gt;
One of New Mexico's best-kept secrets, we are located in southeastern New Mexico, nestled between the two larger cities. &lt;br&gt;
Our town offers a great school system, a small-town atmosphere, and tons of activities and something fun for every age.</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Cardiology Non Invasive</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Artesia</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>NM</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115954</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-Time, Permanent Family Medicine Opportunity in Southwest NM</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>A hospital-affiliated family practice clinic in New Mexico is seeking a full-time Staff Family Medicine Physician to join their growing team. &lt;br&gt;
 Position Highlights: &lt;br&gt;
FT Employee Status&lt;br&gt;
Rural Health Clinic setting&lt;br&gt;
Competitive starting salary plus CME allowance&lt;br&gt;
Work Week 4.5 days per week with one half day of Administrative time for charting, call backs etc.&lt;br&gt;
Broad Scoped Family Practice with Peds, Walk Ins and Chronic Care Patients with Multiple Comorbidities&lt;br&gt;
Facility does participate in ACO&lt;br&gt;
Splinting of simple fractures, a plus with referral to local Orthopedic team&lt;br&gt;
Simple Procedures such as excisional and punch biopsies, simple laceration repairs and I &amp;amp; D of simple abscesses a plus.&lt;br&gt;
ACLS and PALS preferred&lt;br&gt;
ER support located right next door&lt;br&gt;
Health, Dental, LTD and ADD Medical, Dental, Life Insurance 401K / 403B HSA FLEX / FSA&lt;br&gt;
 Facility Details: &lt;br&gt;
Professional development opportunities&lt;br&gt;
Tuition reimbursement program&lt;br&gt;
Continuing education and clinical resources&lt;br&gt;
Benefits: 401K, healthcare insurance, life insurance and much more&lt;br&gt;
Other benefits may include sign-on bonus, relocation assistance and CME allowance&lt;br&gt;
 Location Highlights:  &lt;br&gt;
One of New Mexico's best-kept secrets, we are located in southeastern New Mexico, nestled between the two larger cities. &lt;br&gt;
Our town offers a great school system, a small-town atmosphere, and tons of activities and something fun for every age.</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Family Medicine</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Artesia</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>NM</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115958</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time, Permanent ENT Position in Southwest NM</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Seeking full-time ENT physician for a sole community hospital in Southwest New Mexico, near the Texas border. &lt;br&gt;
 Position Highlights: &lt;br&gt;
Monday  -  Friday 8-5 with &amp;frac12; administrative day&lt;br&gt;
Good General Surgery, Medical specialty and Anesthesia support&lt;br&gt;
Very competitive compensation&lt;br&gt;
Paid malpractice insurance, DEA, controlled substance, and society dues&lt;br&gt;
Paid CME&lt;br&gt;
Community-run facility with 39 beds&lt;br&gt;
Good payor mix and strong community support&lt;br&gt;
 ENT Surgical Procedures to include the following. Contact us today to learn more. &lt;br&gt;
Ear&lt;br&gt;
Larynx&lt;br&gt;
Nasal /  Sinus &lt;br&gt;
Neck&lt;br&gt;
Pediatric &lt;br&gt;
Throat &lt;br&gt;
Thyroid / Parathyroid</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Otolaryngology - Ear, Nose &amp; Throat</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Artesia</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>NM</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116446</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Permanent / W-2 CRNA - northeastern Pennsylvania - 116446/116535</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Permanent / W-2 Nurse Anesthetist (CRNA) - northeastern Pennsylvania &lt;br&gt;
Must be comfortable with most cases.&lt;br&gt;
Hard working, well rounded, experienced in a variety of background and settings.&lt;br&gt;
Assignments limited to one hospital and the ambulatory surgery centers&lt;br&gt;
8hr shifts, call is possible.&lt;br&gt;
Flexible scheduling that provides a greater work/life balance.  &lt;br&gt;
Certifications Required: ACLS and BLS&lt;br&gt;
Board Certified or Eligible Accepted: Board Certified is preferred&lt;br&gt;
Cases: All cases, but this is negotiable&lt;br&gt;
All ages&lt;br&gt;
12 weeks PTO&lt;br&gt;
W2 and 1099 options&lt;br&gt;
Facility offers minimally invasive robotic-assisted procedures and advanced treatment for a wide-range of surgical subspecialties, including orthopedic surgery, neurosurgery&lt;br&gt;
Covid-19 Vaccine Required: Yes</JobDescription>
			<Profession>CRNA</Profession>
			<Specialty>Anesthesia General</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Maryville</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>IL</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116448</JobID>
			<JobTitle>W2 Certified Registered Nurse Practitioner - CRNP, NP - Geriatrics - southwest Pennsylvania - 116448</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>W2 Certified Registered Nurse Practitioner - CRNP, NP - Geriatrics - southwest Pennsylvania &lt;br&gt;
Rural, supportive, and caring community&lt;br&gt;
NP and long-term care experience preferred &lt;br&gt;
M-F day shift&lt;br&gt;
8.5 hrs&lt;br&gt;
DEA, BLS, and CPR&lt;br&gt;
With holidays off and scheduling flexibility.&lt;br&gt;
Must have active state license&lt;br&gt;
Competitive salary, negotiable based on experience + Additional income opportunities.&lt;br&gt;
Stipend to pay for individual licensure renewals&lt;br&gt;
Robust benefits package&lt;br&gt;
All tools and resources supplied&lt;br&gt;
 </JobDescription>
			<Profession>Nurse Practitioner</Profession>
			<Specialty>Geriatrics</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Butler</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>PA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114615</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Permanent Primary Care (FM/IM) Primary Care Opportunity in Southern Oregon! - 114615</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Primary Care (FM/IM) Primary Care Opportunity in Southern Oregon! - 114615 &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
Outpatient only&lt;br&gt;
Candidates must be BC/BE in Family or Internal Medicine. &lt;br&gt;
Schedule/Shifts: flexible scheduling options, no call or inpatient work required&lt;br&gt;
Pay: Competitive compensation with incentives, sign-on bonus, relocation assistance, and great benefits and PTO&lt;br&gt;
State: Oregon&lt;br&gt;
Job Number: 114615</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Primary Care (FM/IM)</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Medford</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114617</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Fulltime/W2 primary care NP/PA opportunity in stunning southern Oregon (OR) - 114617</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Fulltime/W2 primary care NP/PA opportunity in stunning southern Oregon (OR) - 114617 &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
Schedule/Shifts: flexible scheduling options, no call or inpatient work required&lt;br&gt;
Compensation: competitive, great incentives, sign-on bonus, relocation assistance, great PTO and benefits&lt;br&gt;
State: Oregon&lt;br&gt;
Job Number: 114617</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Primary Care (FM/IM)</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Medford</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114618</JobID>
			<JobTitle>W2 Hospitalist Opportunity in beautiful southern Oregon - 114618</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>W2 Hospitalist Opportunity in beautiful southern Oregon - 114618 &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
This is a full-time position with flexible block scheduling&lt;br&gt;
Candidates must be BC/BE in Internal Medicine&lt;br&gt;
level III Trauma Center&lt;br&gt;
Competitive pay with incentives, sign-on bonus, relocation assistance, and excellent benefits&lt;br&gt;
State: Oregon&lt;br&gt;
Job number: 114618</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Hospitalist</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Medford</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114621</JobID>
			<JobTitle>W2 General Neuro NP/PA Opportunity in Southern Oregon! - 114621</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>General Neuro NP Opportunity in Southern Oregon! - 114621 &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
100% outpatient role&lt;br&gt;
competitive base salary + incentives&lt;br&gt;
sign-on bonus&lt;br&gt;
Relocation assistance&lt;br&gt;
great PTO&lt;br&gt;
Excellent healthcare benefits&lt;br&gt;
State: Oregon&lt;br&gt;
Job Number: 114621</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Neurology Adult</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Medford</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114622</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Neurology MD Opportunity for W2/Fulltime Candidates! - Southern Oregon - 114622</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Neurology MD Opportunity for W2/Fulltime Candidates! - Southern Oregon - 114622 &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
Specialty: General neurologist; must be BC/BE&lt;br&gt;
Primarily outpatient with a small amount of inpatient practice&lt;br&gt;
Competitive base salary&lt;br&gt;
Annual incentives&lt;br&gt;
Sign-on bonus&lt;br&gt;
Relocation assistance&lt;br&gt;
Fantastic PTO&lt;br&gt;
Excellent healthcare benefits&lt;br&gt;
State: Oregon&lt;br&gt;
Job Number: 114622</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Neurology Adult</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Medford</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114636</JobID>
			<JobTitle>3 W2 Radiologists Needed in New Jersey ASAP! - 114636</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Needs: Radiologists X 1 Mammographer X 2 Body Imager  &lt;br&gt;
 Competitive salary  &lt;br&gt;
 Highlights &lt;br&gt;
Full-time positions &lt;br&gt;
No night shifts required. &lt;br&gt;
Teaching opportunities with residents and medical students&lt;br&gt;
Emphasis on patient experience, quality and safety&lt;br&gt;
Home workstations supplied&lt;br&gt;
Secure employment with low physician turnover&lt;br&gt;
Potential for career advancement in administrative, utilization review, quality or educational roles&lt;br&gt;
On-site parking</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Radiology</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Camden</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>NJ</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115239</JobID>
			<JobTitle>permanent - Operating Room Manager - Pennsylvania - 115239</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;
Primary Function:&lt;br&gt;
Under the direction of the Director of Perioperative services the Operating Room manager is responsible for coordinating all nursing care and related activities of the Operating Room in coordination with Pre-Op and PACU managers, Material Management, and Central Processing to deliver high quality patient outcomes.&lt;br&gt;
Essential Duties:&lt;br&gt;
Performs essential duties in accordance with established standards of Perioperative Nursing practice.&lt;br&gt;
Collaborates with staff, physicians and other hospital leaders to ensure patient needs are met and quality out comes are achieved.&lt;br&gt;
Ensure the staff is adhering to Hospital policies and procedures&lt;br&gt;
Identifies the need to evaluate and revise nursing policies and procedures as changes occur in the perioperative arena.&lt;br&gt;
Participates in quality improvement programs and initiatives.&lt;br&gt;
Conducts and attends weekly staff meetings and in-services in collaboration with the Nurse Educator.&lt;br&gt;
Promotes cost effectiveness within the department through the management of time and resources.&lt;br&gt;
Demonstrates adaptability, flexibility, and accountability when necessary changes are made to the job description.&lt;br&gt;
Maintains appropriate certifications and professional organization memberships.&lt;br&gt;
They see 45 to 50 cases day and can add up to 10-12 if needed. They do general surgery and have robotics, a heart room, ortho room and robotics. &lt;br&gt;
EMR is EPIC &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Qualifications: &lt;br&gt;
Education &amp;amp; Training:&lt;br&gt;
BSN required, MSN preferred&lt;br&gt;
CNOR preferred and required within 1 year&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Experience:&lt;br&gt;
5 years clinical experience in the Operating Room&lt;br&gt;
2 years&amp;#39; experience in Leadership/Management&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
License, Certification &amp;amp; Registration:&lt;br&gt;
Current licensure as a Registered Nurse in the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania required&lt;br&gt;
BLS Certification through American Heart Association required &lt;br&gt;
ACLS &amp;amp; PALS certification through American Heart Association preferred &lt;br&gt;
Full Time / 40 hours weekly  -  5 days a week / 8am-4:30pm&lt;br&gt;
No on call requirements&lt;br&gt;
The salary is based on a variety of factors: &lt;br&gt;
Years of RN exp,&lt;br&gt;
Years of Nurse Manager exp,&lt;br&gt;
Education &lt;br&gt;
Leadership Certifications&lt;br&gt;
# of direct reports (TBD) - Typically 130&lt;br&gt;
Everyone is eligible for the same annual increases based on performance&lt;br&gt;
There is a Manager Incentive Plan (Bonus): Payment is based on a combination of individual goal achievement and organization goal achievement (candidate can discuss in more detail during the interview)</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>General Surgery</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Philadelphia</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>PA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116473</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time, Permanent General Surgery Opportunity in Southwest NM</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Seeking a full-time General Surgeon to join another full-time General surgeon with anticipation of retirement in next 12-18 months.  &lt;br&gt;
 Position Highlights: &lt;br&gt;
Surgeries include but are not limited to, Colonoscopies&lt;br&gt;
Paid malpractice insurance, DEA, controlled substance, and society dues&lt;br&gt;
Paid CME&lt;br&gt;
Community-run facility with 49 beds&lt;br&gt;
ER visits average about 1,000 per month or 12,000 per year&lt;br&gt;
Good payor mix and strong community support&lt;br&gt;
 Located in rural Southeast New Mexico adjacent to West Texas border. </JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>General Surgery</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Artesia</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>NM</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116474</JobID>
			<JobTitle>W2 Nurse Clinical Educator needed in NJ - 116474</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;
Nurse Clinical Educator&lt;br&gt;
Experience: 5 years Oncology experience preferred&lt;br&gt;
Schedule: Day Mon-Fri 8a-4:30p&lt;br&gt;
Certifications: Oncology strongly desired&lt;br&gt;
NJ Licensed RN. Will accept compact license&lt;br&gt;
Pay range: Varies based on RN license: $48.48- $66.28&lt;br&gt;
Benefit package: Medical, Dental, Vision, Voluntary benefits, PTO, retirement, Tuition reimbursement for eligible positions. &lt;br&gt;
We are a magnet facility; 2nd largest healthcare provider in the tristate.&lt;br&gt;
Hospital/Clinic Equipment Available for Specialty (hospital EMR, MRI, Ultrasound, robotics, etc.)&lt;br&gt;
Support staff: The educator will provide training and educational knowledge to support the nursing team in the designated specialty&lt;br&gt;
Covid vaccine required, unless exemption cleared.&lt;br&gt;
Credentialing &amp;amp; Licensing Timelines: Must be a licensed RN prior to start date&lt;br&gt;
3 panel interviews</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Registered Nurse</Profession>
			<Specialty>Registered Nurse</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Philadelphia</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>PA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116475</JobID>
			<JobTitle>W2 Registered Nurse Educator needed in multiple NJ locations - 116475</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;
Nurse Clinical Educator&lt;br&gt;
Experience: 5 years Oncology experience preferred&lt;br&gt;
Schedule: Day Mon-Fri 8a-4:30p&lt;br&gt;
Certifications: Oncology strongly desired&lt;br&gt;
NJ Licensed RN. Will accept compact license&lt;br&gt;
Pay range: Varies based on RN license: $48.48- $66.28&lt;br&gt;
Benefit package: Medical, Dental, Vision, Voluntary benefits, PTO, retirement, Tuition reimbursement for eligible positions. &lt;br&gt;
We are a magnet facility; 2nd largest healthcare provider in the tristate.&lt;br&gt;
Hospital/Clinic Equipment Available for Specialty (hospital EMR, MRI, Ultrasound, robotics, etc.)&lt;br&gt;
Support staff: The educator will provide training and educational knowledge to support the nursing team in the designated specialty&lt;br&gt;
Covid vaccine required, unless exemption cleared.&lt;br&gt;
Credentialing &amp;amp; Licensing Timelines: Must be a licensed RN prior to start date&lt;br&gt;
3 panel interviews</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Registered Nurse</Profession>
			<Specialty>Registered Nurse</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Philadelphia</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>PA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116861</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Permanent/Fulltime CRNA - Central PA - 116861</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Permanent/Fulltime CRNA - Central PA - 116861 &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
Specialty: CRNA&lt;br&gt;
Start: August 2023&lt;br&gt;
Schedule: 7:30-5pm M-F (Managed in house) no call or weekend commitment required&lt;br&gt;
Highlights: Great quality of life- No Call&lt;br&gt;
5-6 weeks of vacation&lt;br&gt;
Benefits are strong&lt;br&gt;
Outstanding support structure with nursing and GI assistance.&lt;br&gt;
Primarily endoscopic (colonoscopy and EGD)&lt;br&gt;
Shifts needed (Mon-Fri; 8-hours - 2 rooms Monday Friday, 3 Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday&lt;br&gt;
EMR: Centrisity (minimal training needed)&lt;br&gt;
State: Pennsylvania&lt;br&gt;
Job number: 116861</JobDescription>
			<Profession>CRNA</Profession>
			<Specialty>Anesthesia General</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Altoona</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>PA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116125</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time, Permanent Radiology Opportunity in the Cascade Mountains of Washington | 116125</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Join our team of Radiologists including Breast Imagers, Chest Imaging, MSK, Body Imaging, Neuroradiology, and Interventional Radiology. &lt;br&gt;
 Position Highlights: &lt;br&gt;
Full-time position&lt;br&gt;
4 or 5-day schedule available&lt;br&gt;
No night call&lt;br&gt;
Chest and Body imagers work closely with their subspecialty colleagues&lt;br&gt;
Responsibilities: general diagnostic radiology (excluding mammography), as well as routine fluoroscopic &amp;amp; ultrasound-guided procedures.&lt;br&gt;
EPIC Electronic Medical Record&lt;br&gt;
J1 candidates considered&lt;br&gt;
Recognized as an organization committed to improving provider satisfaction and reducing burnout.&lt;br&gt;
First-year salary guarantee based on MGMA/AMGA median&lt;br&gt;
RVU production in year two&lt;br&gt;
Signing bonus, up to 11 weeks off per year, matching 401k, life insurance, long-term disability insurance, plus more&lt;br&gt;
Relocation expenses covered including packing - up to $20,000&lt;br&gt;
Continuing medical education allowance of $8,000 every two years&lt;br&gt;
Generous healthcare stipend of $618 per month to cover healthcare benefits and more&lt;br&gt;
Student Loan Counseling for the life of your student loan repayment&lt;br&gt;
Vital Work Life Employee Assistance Program &lt;br&gt;
1-year physician partnership track for US candidates&lt;br&gt;
Physician leaders and decision-makers at all levels of the organization&lt;br&gt;
Influence and say in the practice&lt;br&gt;
 What We Are Seeking in a Candidate &lt;br&gt;
Board-certified or board-eligible Radiologist &lt;br&gt;
With fellowship training in Chest or Body Imaging&lt;br&gt;
Ability to obtain an active license in Washington State&lt;br&gt;
Concise communication skills to educate patients and families compassionately&lt;br&gt;
Thoroughly document and maintain patient records comprehensively&lt;br&gt;
 Location Highlights: &lt;br&gt;
Surrounded by opportunities for  white water rafting, hiking, fishing, camping, skiing, snowboarding, kayaking, and backpacking &lt;br&gt;
Family-friendly environment with safe communities &lt;br&gt;
Lots of music, culture, and arts for the family</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Radiology</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Wenatchee</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>WA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116126</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time, Permanent CRNA Opportunity in the Cascade Mountains of Washington | 116126 / 116541</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Full-time, Permanent CRNA Opportunity in the Cascade Mountains of Washington | 116126 / 116541 &lt;br&gt;
 Position Highlights: &lt;br&gt;
Competitive annual salary&lt;br&gt;
Care Team Model &amp;amp; outstanding Anesthesia colleagues&lt;br&gt;
Monday-Friday 7-3 schedule &lt;br&gt;
No call responsibilities&lt;br&gt;
Work / Life Balance and Benefits&lt;br&gt;
Recognized as an organization committed to improving provider satisfaction and reducing burnout.&lt;br&gt;
$25,000 signing bonus with a two-year commitment&lt;br&gt;
Matching 401k, life insurance, long-term disability insurance, plus more&lt;br&gt;
Student loan repayment of up to $24,000&lt;br&gt;
Relocation stipend of $5,000 in the first paycheck&lt;br&gt;
30 days PTO 1st year&lt;br&gt;
Continuing medical education allowance of $4,000 every two years&lt;br&gt;
Generous healthcare benefits&lt;br&gt;
Mentoring program&lt;br&gt;
 Required: &lt;br&gt;
WA state RN and ARNP License, completion of CRNA national certification&lt;br&gt;
Preferred 2 years of experience, but new grads very welcome&lt;br&gt;
Fully vaccinated against COVID-19 (Religious and medical exemptions will be considered upon request.)&lt;br&gt;
 Location Highlights: &lt;br&gt;
Surrounded by opportunities for  white water rafting, hiking, fishing, camping, skiing, snowboarding, kayaking, and backpacking &lt;br&gt;
Family-friendly environment with safe communities &lt;br&gt;
Lots of music, culture, and arts for the family</JobDescription>
			<Profession>CRNA</Profession>
			<Specialty>Anesthesia General</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Wenatchee</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>WA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116127</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time, Permanent Oncology Position in the Cascade Mountains of Washington | 116127</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Seeking an Oncologist to join a multi-specialty healthcare organization committed to taking care of its physicians and patients.    &lt;br&gt;
 Position Highlights: &lt;br&gt;
Join well-trained Medical Oncologists, Radiation Oncologists, Advanced Practice Providers, as well as Certified Oncology Nurses, Dieticians, Pharmacists, Behavioral Med Practitioners, Palliative Care, etc.&lt;br&gt;
Full-time position, four-day work week available&lt;br&gt;
Regional cancer care program that is busy, well-established, successful, comprehensive, and accredited&lt;br&gt;
Radiation treatment and infusion center in-house &lt;br&gt;
Epic Electronic Medical Record&lt;br&gt;
Recognized as an organization committed to improving physician satisfaction and reducing burnout.&lt;br&gt;
First-year salary guarantee based on MGMA/AMGA median&lt;br&gt;
RVU production in year two. &lt;br&gt;
Placement in a starting range is based on training, experience, certifications, etc. &lt;br&gt;
Actual salaries will vary based on a candidate's qualifications.&lt;br&gt;
Time off: up to 11 weeks (for full-time, five-day production work week after the first year, non-immigration status) of time off&lt;br&gt;
Relocation expenses covered including packing: up to $20,000&lt;br&gt;
Continuing medical education allowance of $8,000 every two years&lt;br&gt;
Generous Healthcare/Vision/Dental Annual Premium paid for provider and family&lt;br&gt;
Matching 401k upon start, life insurance, long-term disability insurance&lt;br&gt;
Signing bonus&lt;br&gt;
Student Loan Counseling for the life of your student loan repayment&lt;br&gt;
Vital Work Life Employee Assistance Program &lt;br&gt;
One-year physician partnership track for US candidates&lt;br&gt;
Physician leaders and decision-makers at all levels of the organization&lt;br&gt;
 Requirements: &lt;br&gt;
Board-certified or board-eligible Medical Oncologist&lt;br&gt;
Ability to obtain an active license in Washington State&lt;br&gt;
Providers who value high-quality care and work/life balance&lt;br&gt;
Concise and compassionate communication skills to educate patients and families &lt;br&gt;
Ability to document and maintain patient records thoroughly and accurately&lt;br&gt;
Fully vaccinated against COVID-19 (Religious and medical exemptions will be considered upon request)</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Oncology</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Wenatchee</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>WA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116513</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Permanent CRNA positions open throughout Pennsylvania - 116513</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Permanent CRNA positions open throughout Pennsylvania - 116513 &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
Specialty: CRNA&lt;br&gt;
Shifts can include 8 or 12 hour shifts plus weekend and evening call is needed&lt;br&gt;
Procedures include but not limited to OB, GI, Dental, eyes, ortho, Heads and Hearts (Cardiac), Trauma Level 1 (metro area shootings, stabbings, etc.); No transplants&lt;br&gt;
This client can accommodate all needs and desires depending on the CRNA. (from flexible, non trauma cases to very extreme life-threatening needs)&lt;br&gt;
Mix of supervisory from Anesthesiologists and a mix of doing their own cases&lt;br&gt;
State: Pennsylvania&lt;br&gt;
Job number: 116513</JobDescription>
			<Profession>CRNA</Profession>
			<Specialty>Anesthesia General</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Philadelphia</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>PA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115650</JobID>
			<JobTitle>permanent - Regional Vice President ASC Operations - 115650</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;
Type: Direct Hire&lt;br&gt;
Title: Regional Vice President ASC Operations &lt;br&gt;
Location: Must live in North NJ, NY, or commutable to territory weekly &lt;br&gt;
Travel: Travel throughout NY up to 50% of the time&lt;br&gt;
Be mindful of any non-compete issues and disclose this information &lt;br&gt;
Bonus: 40% of annual salary&lt;br&gt;
# of Direct Reports: No direct reports, many in-direct reports at the centers and lots of department collaboration with corporate and clinical on Managed Service Organization side.&lt;br&gt;
Extensive Details:&lt;ol start="1" type="1"&gt;&lt;ul type="circle"&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Advanced degrees, MBA, MHA, or others are a plus&lt;br&gt;
At least 5 years' experience in a healthcare service operations role with a strong emphasis in strategic planning and financial performance management&lt;br&gt;
Experience working and traveling to multiple sites (ideally in NY)&lt;br&gt;
5+ years of working with healthcare providers in a leadership capacity. &lt;br&gt;
Experience managing relationships with physicians (owning physicians, board, medical directors, etc.)&lt;br&gt;
Ideally, prior experience with single-specialty or multi-specialty Ambulatory Surgery Centers the following will also work&lt;ol&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Practice, hospital, or OBS (office based surgery) - as long as more about strategic growth and not operations&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Ideally, for profit management experience in a managed service organization the following will also work&lt;ol&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Large practice group or hospital joint venture setting where they focused primarily on the successful operations and growth of multiple locations.&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Strong understanding of financials and operations - ability to look at financial and operational deficiencies, see trouble coming and fix proactively.&lt;br&gt;
Should have experience in Revenue Cycle/ Billing experience&lt;br&gt;
Experience with mergers and acquisitions  -  we would love someone who has developed new business or been a part of that process. &lt;br&gt;
Experience with physician recruitment, organic growth succession planning, and patient access&lt;/ol&gt;</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Administrative Staff</Profession>
			<Specialty>Gastroenterology</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Jamison</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>PA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115667</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full Time - Permanent - Operating Room Nurse Manager - RN - Elkins Park, PA</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Full Time - Permanent - Operating Room Nurse Manager - RN - Elkins Park, PA  &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
Bachelor&amp;#39;s degree in Nursing preferred.&lt;br&gt;
Current Pennsylvania RN license.&lt;br&gt;
CPR certification.&lt;br&gt;
1-2 years of OR Experience required.&lt;br&gt;
Successful completion of a perioperative course would be considered in lieu of minimum years of experience.&lt;br&gt;
Successful completion of a skills based test required.&lt;br&gt;
Travel between Einstein locations required.&lt;br&gt;
Serving as a member of the surgical team by planning the perioperative care for surgical patients.&lt;br&gt;
Participating in the identification and resolution of nursing practice and unit problems.</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Registered Nurse</Profession>
			<Specialty>General Surgery</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Philadelphia</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>PA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115698</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full time CRNA positions open in Texas - Flexible schedule - 115698</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;
Client needs 14-20 FTE (CRNA)&lt;br&gt;
Would appreciate candidates with a wide range of exp (General, Otho, GI, etc.&amp;hellip;)&lt;br&gt;
ACT Model: Limited OB, No regional Neuro Block, No peripherals&lt;br&gt;
33 Operating Rooms, 2 reserve.&lt;br&gt;
Salary range is $180k (New Grad), $210  (5 years exp) and up&amp;hellip;&lt;br&gt;
Overtime is plentiful and can allow for a great increase in pay - $140/ hr. for Weekday and $160 / hour Weekend.&lt;br&gt;
Flexible Schedule: 8, 10, 12 or 13 hour shifts&lt;br&gt;
Weekday call is 1x per month.&lt;br&gt;
Benefits- 401k, Medical, Dental Vision &lt;br&gt;
7k relocation assistance (as needed) &lt;br&gt;
$4000 CME + 5 days of CME&lt;br&gt;
5 Weeks PTO&lt;br&gt;
No State income Tax&lt;br&gt;
$100k sign on bonus  (50k after 30 days, 25k at the start of candidate's 2nd year and the remaining 25k at the start of year 3)&lt;br&gt;
Fully Funded MHA&lt;br&gt;
Interview process will move fast  -  Prompt name clear then a 24 - 48-hour response to set up interview set up. Will meet regional and local CRNA leadership. &lt;br&gt;
Well respected health system </JobDescription>
			<Profession>CRNA</Profession>
			<Specialty>Anesthesia General</Specialty>
			<SiteState>TX</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116638</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Fulltime/Permanent - NP's &amp; PA's - Urgent Care and Primary Care locations in OR, WA, MT, WY, and CO - 116638</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Fulltime/Permanent - NP&amp;#39;s &amp;amp; PA&amp;#39;s - Urgent Care and Primary Care locations in OR, WA, MT, WY, and CO - 116638 &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
Specialty: NPs and PAs&lt;br&gt;
Job requirements:&lt;br&gt;
Provide care generally on an outpatient basis and such pre-operative care in minor surgery normally performed on an outpatient basis. &lt;br&gt;
Responsible for the delivery of care, treatment, and referrals. Arrange for referral resources for those medical specialties not provided by the organization for patients of the clinic. &lt;br&gt;
Physician Assistant or Nurse Practitioner who functions as an independent healthcare provider who, working collaboratively within a multidisciplinary health team, is responsible for providing comprehensive care to patients with acute or chronic medical conditions in a urgent care setting. &lt;br&gt;
The PA or NP demonstrates a high degree of clinical expertise in working with patients with acute and chronic illnesses or acute injuries commonly encountered in both the pediatric and adult patient population. &lt;br&gt;
The provider is responsible for assessment, diagnosis, treatment, management, education, health promotion and care coordination for patients and families with acute and chronic. &lt;br&gt;
Knowledge of treatment and drug interactions.&lt;br&gt;
Excellent communication and interpersonal skills.&lt;br&gt;
Evaluate patients, based on medical training and/or specialty, to determine the medical condition of the patient, through the performance of physical examinations, thereby establishing a diagnosis and proposed treatment plan.&lt;br&gt;
Perform such clinical procedures for patient&amp;#39;s benefit which are within scope and skill of practitioner, and which are economically feasible.&lt;br&gt;
Communicate information to patients regarding diagnosis and treatment goals.&lt;br&gt;
Maintains accurate, complete, concise and timely documentation in the electronic medical record.&lt;br&gt;
Shifts:&lt;br&gt;
Our Urgent Care clinics are open 7 days a week.&lt;br&gt;
Open 8am to 8pm. Shifts are 3  -  12's per week. (158-166 hours per month).&lt;br&gt;
Shifts are 3  -  12's per week. (158-166 hours per month).&lt;br&gt;
Primary Care clinics are open M-F 8am to 6pm.&lt;br&gt;
Providers see patients 4 days a week and we reserve 1 day a week for admin/charting (no patients).&lt;br&gt;
Rotating On-Call shifts (2x a month +/-) with Same benefit package.&lt;br&gt;
Benefits:&lt;br&gt;
Full Benefits.  &lt;br&gt;
The client is accredited and provider in-house CME's.  Plus paid 36 hours of CME time.  &lt;br&gt;
Annual License Renewal and a yearly subscription to Up-to-Date.&lt;br&gt;
State: OR, WA, MT, WY, and CO&lt;br&gt;
Job number: 116638</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Nurse Practitioner</Profession>
			<Specialty>Urgent Care</Specialty>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>114040</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Permanent Anesthesiologists Needed in the Greater Philadelphia Area (PA) - 114040</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;
Perm Anesthesiologists Needed in the Greater Philadelphia Area - 114040Specialties: &lt;br&gt;
2 Pediatric, 2 Cardiology,  8 General Anesthesiologists&lt;br&gt;
Compensation:&lt;br&gt;
Competitive Salary&lt;br&gt;
Sign-on Bonus&lt;br&gt;
Relocation assistance&lt;br&gt;
 Benefits &amp;amp; Perks:  &lt;br&gt;
Highly Competitive compensation with a superb benefits package&lt;br&gt;
Variety of site, specialty, and schedule &lt;br&gt;
Low-cost health insurance for employees and their families&lt;br&gt;
Generous CME allowance&lt;br&gt;
Top-tier retirement programs&lt;br&gt;
Malpractice Insurance with Tail Coverage &lt;br&gt;
Relocation Assistance&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Practice /Position Overview: &lt;br&gt;
Seeking anesthesiologists with a variety of clinical interests and expertise, with emphasis on general and orthopedic anesthesia, cardiovascular anesthesia, pediatric anesthesia, obstetric anesthesia, and neuroanesthesia, as our network continues to grow and add to the scale and clinical specialization of the care we deliver.&lt;br&gt;
Opportunities for diverse practice experience of case and facility type, or focused practice geographically or clinically.&lt;br&gt;
Opportunities for facility and subspecialty leadership and professional development. An opportunity to explore clinical research is available and will be supported.&lt;br&gt;
 Job Qualifications: &lt;br&gt;
Passion for clinical work to positively impact patient care, safety, and experience.&lt;br&gt;
Must be Board Eligible or Board Certified with the American Board of Anesthesiology&lt;br&gt;
A valid Pennsylvania Medical License or the ability to obtain one is required&lt;br&gt;
 Influenza vaccination and COVID-19 Vaccination is required for all colleagues unless medically contraindicated or due to a bona fide religious belief or practice. Applicants possessing a medical marijuana card will not be considered for safety-sensitive positions. EOE. &lt;br&gt;
 </JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Anesthesia General</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Allentown</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>PA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115417</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time W2 Director of Anesthesia (Anesthesiologist) is Needed in Manhattan (NY) - 115417</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Full-time W2 Director of Anesthesia (Anesthesiologist) is Needed in Manhattan (NY) - 115417 &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
Position type: Anesthesiologist&lt;br&gt;
Types of cases: EGD, CS, Flex Sig, HET  &lt;br&gt;
Board Certified or Board Eligibility status: Board Certified &lt;br&gt;
Exact hours, any evenings or weekends expected: M-F First cases start roughly 7:00a last case start avg. 4:00p/4:30p. &lt;br&gt;
Benefits: .m/d/v/p offered; paid holidays and additional perks and coverage&lt;br&gt;
State: New York&lt;br&gt;
Job Number: 115417</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Anesthesia General</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Jamison</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>PA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115699</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full time CRNA positions open in Texas - Flexible schedule - 115699</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;br&gt;
Client needs 14-20 FTE (CRNA)&lt;br&gt;
Would appreciate candidates with a wide range of exp (General, Otho, GI, etc.&amp;hellip;)&lt;br&gt;
ACT Model: Limited OB, No regional Neuro Block, No peripherals&lt;br&gt;
33 Operating Rooms, 2 reserve.&lt;br&gt;
Salary range is $180k (New Grad), $210  (5 years exp) and up&amp;hellip;&lt;br&gt;
Overtime is plentiful and can allow for a great increase in pay - $140/ hr. for Weekday and $160 / hour Weekend.&lt;br&gt;
Flexible Schedule: 8, 10, 12 or 13 hour shifts&lt;br&gt;
Weekday call is 1x per month.&lt;br&gt;
Benefits- 401k, Medical, Dental Vision &lt;br&gt;
7k relocation assistance (as needed) &lt;br&gt;
$4000 CME + 5 days of CME&lt;br&gt;
5 Weeks PTO&lt;br&gt;
No State income Tax&lt;br&gt;
$100k sign on bonus  (50k after 30 days, 25k at the start of candidate's 2nd year and the remaining 25k at the start of year 3)&lt;br&gt;
Fully Funded MHA&lt;br&gt;
Interview process will move fast  -  Prompt name clear then a 24 - 48-hour response to set up interview set up. Will meet regional and local CRNA leadership. &lt;br&gt;
Well respected health system </JobDescription>
			<Profession>CRNA</Profession>
			<Specialty>Anesthesia General</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Central</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>TX</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116246</JobID>
			<JobTitle>W-2/Permanent Pediatrician MD/DO - southeast Iowa - 116246</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>W-2/Permanent Pediatrician MD/DO - southeast Iowa &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
Willing to wait for a state license&lt;br&gt;
Vaccination Preferred, but religious/medical exemptions are possible&lt;br&gt;
Certifications required: BC/BE, BLS, PALS&lt;br&gt;
Background Experience: 3+ years; Outpatient care with children&lt;br&gt;
Iowa CSR&lt;br&gt;
Patient Volume: 18-22 ppd&lt;br&gt;
Common cases: cold/flu, sinus infections, physicals, immunizations, rashes, allergies, asthma&lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
 </JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Pediatrics</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>West Burlington</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>IA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116305</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Permanent / W-2 CRNA - northwest Oregon - 116305 / 116545</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Permanent / W-2 CRNA - northwest Oregon &lt;br&gt;
Currently hiring at all the nearby locations&lt;br&gt;
Client provides CRNA services at multiple hospitals, surgery centers, and clinics in the Willamette Valley and surrounding communities of the Pacific Northwest.&lt;br&gt;
Patient Care is number one. Looking for someone to integrate with the community.&lt;br&gt;
Board Certified or Eligible Accepted: Yes&lt;br&gt;
Call 1 in 6&lt;br&gt;
Patient Ages: Adult&lt;br&gt;
7 providers, no OB&lt;br&gt;
Covid-19 Vaccine Required: Yes</JobDescription>
			<Profession>CRNA</Profession>
			<Specialty>Anesthesia General</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Portland</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>115479</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Fulltime/W2 Emergency Medicine Physician Opportunity in Southern Oregon - 115479</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Fulltime/W2 Emergency Medicine Physician Opportunity in Southern Oregon - 115479 &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
Candidates must be BC/BE in Emergency Medicine (ABEM)&lt;br&gt;
Site: Level III trauma center&lt;br&gt;
Competitive hourly rate&lt;br&gt;
Annual performance incentives&lt;br&gt;
Evening shift differential&lt;br&gt;
Signing bonus&lt;br&gt;
Relocation assistance&lt;br&gt;
Annual CME allowance&lt;br&gt;
Generous time off accrual plan&lt;br&gt;
Excellent health, dental, vision, and retirement benefits&lt;br&gt;
State: Oregon&lt;br&gt;
Job Number: 115479</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Emergency Medicine</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Medford</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116347</JobID>
			<JobTitle>W-2 / permanent hire Radiologist - northeastern Oregon - 116347</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>W-2 / permanent hire - northeastern Oregon &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
Diagnostic/Interventional Radiologist&lt;br&gt;
Must have active state license&lt;br&gt;
Vaccination Required? Yes&lt;br&gt;
Certifications required: BE or BC, BLS&lt;br&gt;
Must be MQSA&lt;br&gt;
Credentialing: 30-60 days &lt;br&gt;
Start Date: As soon as credentialed&lt;br&gt;
Dates: 7 on  -  7 off Mon-Sun&lt;br&gt;
14 shifts per month&lt;br&gt;
Work Schedule: 6:30A-7P Mon  -  Fri on site&lt;br&gt;
Saturday and Sunday (can work on site or remote doing tele reads)&lt;br&gt;
Call Schedule: No Call&lt;br&gt;
Patient Volume: 140 reads per day</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Radiology</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Enterprise</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>OR</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116369</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time, Permanent MD/DO Pediatrics Opportunity in South Central FL</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Position Highlights: &lt;br&gt;
Outpatient-only&lt;br&gt;
Bilingual English/Spanish is strongly preferred.&lt;br&gt;
Federally Qualified Health Center located near Ft. Meyers, Florida&lt;br&gt;
One of 3.0 FTE physicians (family medicine and pediatrics) and 2 FTE Nurse Practitioners.&lt;br&gt;
Full benefits package including paid time off, education stipend, paid holidays, health insurance, and access to a 403B retirement plan.&lt;br&gt;
National Health Service Corp Site with a community score of 18. The hospital provided educational loan payments available.&lt;br&gt;
Relocation benefits are paid in accordance with current IRS regulations.&lt;br&gt;
 Community: &lt;br&gt;
Located just 45 min drive from Ft. Myers on the Gulf coast and 90 minutes to West Palm on the Atlantic Coast. 120 miles north of Miami and approximately 150 miles south of Orlando.&lt;br&gt;
Enjoy recreational opportunities such as golf, the finest bass fishing lake in the United States (Lake Okeechobee), Birding, hiking horseback riding and hunting.&lt;br&gt;
Experience cultural events such at The Firehouse Theater and many festivals and fairs held throughout the year.&lt;br&gt;
Easy travel to several major metropolitan areas for professional sports (football, baseball, basketball ice hockey and soccer) and college sporting events. &lt;br&gt;
Many convenient options for air travel out of Miami International, Fort Lauderdale, Palm Beach International and Southwest International in Fort Myers.</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Pediatrics</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Clewiston</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>FL</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116370</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Full-time, Permanent Radiology Position in Southeast New Mexico - 116370</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Seeking a Radiologist to join a growing team in SW New Mexico. &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
Prefer current reader - MQSA &lt;br&gt;
Ultrasound Guide biopsy, Interventional Radiologist (CT Guided biopsy, PICC lines, CT guided drainages, Para/Thora,  etc.)&lt;br&gt;
Fluoro procedures&lt;br&gt;
Read all Modalities (Plain film, CT, MRI, Nuc Med, PET Scan, Mammo, US (General, Vascular)&lt;br&gt;
Average Daily Volumes 70-80 reads&lt;br&gt;
Monday  -  Friday (8-5 pm)&lt;br&gt;
Seeking a good communicator, instructor and educator. Willing to help grow the Artesia General radiology department.   &lt;br&gt;
Current on all Imaging techniques and standards of care. &lt;br&gt;
Must have been on a previous Radioactive Materials License (RAM license).&lt;br&gt;
Needs to be comfortable with IR Procedures, have performed then recently&lt;br&gt;
Average about 10 IR cases a week, the rest is Diagnostic, average 70-80 cases a day&lt;br&gt;
Radiologist on-site, TELE-RAD is available for backup on some cases&lt;br&gt;
Call ratio: very rarely called in, use a teleradiology service after hours</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Radiology</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Artesia</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>NM</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116737</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Permanent/Fulltime - Hospitalist - North Carolina - 116737</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;pre&gt;Permanent/Fulltime - Hospitalist - North Carolina - 116737&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;Hospitalist positions are fully employed positions offering a 12 hour shift (15 shifts a month), 7 on 7 off schedule.&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;IM Board Certified/Board Eligible in two years&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;Competitive Salary with Sign-on Bonus&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;Retention Plan&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;Relocation&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;Paid Malpractice w/Tail&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;CME Time and Allowance&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;Generous Benefits Package  -  403(b) match and 457(b); Health and Dental; and other desirable benefits&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;Dedicated Admitter&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;Closed ICU&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;EPIC EMR System&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;State: North Carolina&lt;/pre&gt;</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Hospitalist</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Fayetteville</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>NC</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116738</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Permanent/Fulltime - Urologist - North Carolina - 116738</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;pre&gt;Permanent/Fulltime - Urologist - North Carolina - 116738&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;Specialty: Urologist&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;The scope of services include treatment for prostate, kidney and bladder cancers, kidney stones, vasectomies, sexual dysfunction, urinary incontinence, and other genitourinary disorders. Schedule is Monday - Friday from 8:00 am - 5:00 pm with up to 7 nights of call per month.&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;Benefits include: best in class compensation, sign-on bonus, relocation allowance and a generous benefits including Paid Malpractice, CME Time and Allowance, Accrued Paid Time Off, 403(b) match and 457(b), Health and Dental, and other desirable benefits.&lt;/pre&gt;</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Urology</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Fayetteville</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>NC</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116739</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Permanent/Fulltime - BE/BC Pediatrician - Fayetteville, North Carolina - 116739</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;pre&gt;Permanent/Fulltime - BE/BC Pediatrician - Fayetteville, North Carolina - 116739&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;Specialty: BE/BC Pediatrician&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;Group sees patients up to 18 years of age. Physicians have dedicated exam rooms and a private office. Ancillary services are available.&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;Best in class compensation, sign-on bonus, relocation allowance and a generous benefits including Paid Malpractice, CME Time and Allowance, Accrued Paid Time Off, 403(b) match and 457(b), Health and Dental, and other desirable benefits.&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;State: North Carolina&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;Job number: 116739&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Pediatrics</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Fayetteville</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>NC</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116740</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Permanent/Fulltime - Psychiatry Adult Outpatient Opportunity - North Carolina - 116740</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;pre&gt;Permanent/Fulltime - Psychiatry Adult Outpatient Opportunity - North Carolina - 116740&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;Specialty: Psychiatry Adult Outpatient&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;Best in class compensation plus generous benefits including Paid Malpractice, CME Time and Allowance, Accrued Paid Time Off, 403(b) match and 457(b), Health, Dental, and other desirable benefits.&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;State: North Carolina&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;Job number: 116740&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 </JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Psychiatry</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Fayetteville</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>NC</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116741</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Permanent/Fulltime - OBGYN - North Carolina - 116741</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>&lt;pre&gt;Permanent/Fulltime - OBGYN - North Carolina - 116741&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;Specialty: OBGYN&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;Top Tier Compensation&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;The comprehensive benefits package includes Malpractice Insurance paid, CME Time and Allowance, 403(b) match, 457(b), health, vision, dental, and other desirable benefits.&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;State: North Carolina&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;Job number: 116741&lt;/pre&gt;</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Obstetrics Gynecology</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Fayetteville</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>NC</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116767</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Fulltime/Permanent -  Pediatrician Needed - California - 116767</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Fulltime/Permanent - Pediatric Need - California - 116767 &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
Specialty: Pediatrician&lt;br&gt;
No nights and no weekends, no call.&lt;br&gt;
Shifts: Monday through Friday for the first couple of months, 8-5. Then they can go to 4-10 hour shifts.&lt;br&gt;
Opportunity Highlights&lt;br&gt;
Flexible schedule&lt;br&gt;
Competitive Base Salary Package&lt;br&gt;
Productivity/Incentive Compensation&lt;br&gt;
Commencement Bonus&lt;br&gt;
CME assistance&lt;br&gt;
Relocation Allowance&lt;br&gt;
Education; Experience&lt;br&gt;
MD or DO&lt;br&gt;
Board Certification&lt;br&gt;
California Medical License&lt;br&gt;
Passion for serving underserved patients</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Pediatrics</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Susanville</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>CA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
		<job>
			<JobID>116768</JobID>
			<JobTitle>Fulltime/Permanent - Medical Director - California - 116768</JobTitle>
			<JobDescription>Fulltime/Permanent - Medical Director - California - 116768 &lt;br&gt;
 The Chief Medical Director (CMO) is responsible for the quality of good clinical practice. This is accomplished through the provision of a quality assurance process, monitoring the clinical policies and procedures used to ensure quality of patient care with sensitivity to efficiency and cost effectiveness, and payer contracts. The Medical Director maintains good communication with both the provider staff and the management group, helping to resolve problems related to operational issues affecting patient care services. The CMO is the lead spokesperson for the Medical Staff and represents them at Management and Board meetings. Likewise, the CMO is a management representative to the Medical Staff. The CMO also assists in budget and operational planning providing input into the decision-making process of the clinic as a full member of the management team. &lt;br&gt;
 The CMO position will be 60% management and 40% clinical delivery of service, which would be Primary Care. &lt;br&gt;
 Qualifications &lt;br&gt;
Current license to practice medicine in the State of California.&lt;br&gt;
Certification by an American Medical Specialty Board or licensed.&lt;br&gt;
Current CPR and ACLS certification&lt;br&gt;
Possess current valid California Drivers License and Liability auto insurance.&lt;br&gt;
Ability to use computer to produce reports and other data.&lt;br&gt;
 Duties and Responsibilities &lt;br&gt;
Ensure the provision of basic services delineated in the Principles of Practice, planning and implementing all new medical services.  &lt;br&gt;
Develop and implement medical policy in coordination with staff and CEO.&lt;br&gt;
Ensure that qualified medical personnel render medical decisions.&lt;br&gt;
Assist in the recruitment, hiring, and orientation of medical providers.&lt;br&gt;
Review and ensure appropriate credentialing for all medical personnel.&lt;br&gt;
Ensure that medical protocols and rules of conduct for medical personnel are followed.&lt;br&gt;
Implement disciplinary procedures as appropriate.&lt;br&gt;
Resolve medical-related problems, referring non-medical grievances and grievances, which he/she determines, may be appropriately resolved through the grievance procedure, to the CEO.&lt;br&gt;
Assess needs for continuing medical education and training, making recommendations to CEO.&lt;br&gt;
Participate in and monitor daily clinic operations, including administrative functions.&lt;br&gt;
Coordinate and lead provider staff meetings monthly. Participate in other meetings as appropriate.&lt;br&gt;
Prepare and revise Health Care Plan annually for Federal grant application.&lt;br&gt;
Serve as spokesperson for the medical staff to CEO and Board of Directors.&lt;br&gt;
Responsible for Quality Improvement program.&lt;br&gt;
Supervise Quality Improvement Director, attend QI meetings, monitor and oversee QI activities.&lt;br&gt;
Performs other duties as assigned, demonstrating flexibility and willingness to do extra work as needed, on an intermittent basis.&lt;br&gt;
Maintains strict confidentiality. Does not disclose confidential information regarding patients, co-workers, or the organization to unauthorized individuals in or out of the organization.&lt;br&gt;
Sensitive to customer service issues, displaying a positive attitude to patients, co-workers, and the organization as a whole.&lt;br&gt;
Responsive to supervisory feedback, utilizing constructive criticism in a positive manner.&lt;br&gt;
Maintains open communication and observes chain of command.</JobDescription>
			<Profession>Physician</Profession>
			<Specialty>Primary Care (FM/IM)</Specialty>
			<SiteCity>Susanville</SiteCity>
			<SiteState>CA</SiteState>
			<Recruiter>amber@iconmn.com</Recruiter>
		</job>
	</jobs>
